<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Live Smart]]></title><description><![CDATA[Programming / Investment / Health / Life Hacks]]></description><link>https://live-smart.github.io</link><image><url>https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/19504323/15453331/828a4ae8-2044-11e6-83e3-e1153288e4d9.jpeg</url><title>Live Smart</title><link>https://live-smart.github.io</link></image><generator>RSS for Node</generator><lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2018 14:38:52 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://live-smart.github.io/rss/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><ttl>60</ttl><item><title><![CDATA[3 Unique Gadgets You Wouldn't Expect To Exist]]></title><description><![CDATA[<iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/z5ydE6qQqZU?rel=0" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>would you look at these unusual gadgets
especially this one I&#8217;ve said it before
I&#8217;ll say it again I&#8217;m here to uncover
what&#8217;s happening in the entire realm of
gadgets and today is no different
something here called the Symphonica a
modular system called vibes something
called the mighty you&#8217;re gonna get to
learn about all of them a very formal
intro hmm first I want to kick it off
with this vibes system think of it kind
of like moto mods where you can swap out
an attachment on the back of your device
put on this case here then click in the
sound engine this thing looks pretty
substantial or the battery bank 150
times your battery charger so it&#8217;s kind
of like a bumper so here&#8217;s an s8
just slam it in there this is your fold
getting chunkier benefit is a lot of
protection wow that is a substantial
speaker so this is the charge doc so
that the speaker is ready to go when you
want to take it with you this also has a
kickstand on it and then you have a
speaker you have a Bluetooth speaker
which is stationary wherever you happen
to be you press this release take this
with you this remains plugged in an EQ
button volume up and down play pause
answer phone call okay so clipping it in
is easy my phone is huge now we&#8217;re gonna
listen to that in a second but this is
the volt rocks even though it&#8217;s a type-c
connector to go into the phone it&#8217;s a
micro USB connector to charge this up
you see we have a full charge there 3000
milliamp hours and then all that happens
is this little piece pops out and you
have a type-c connector on the iPhone
version that&#8217;s gonna be lightning same
idea it clips in there into there
and we&#8217;re charging up hopefully this
thing has some battery as well whoa I
was sensual that is why is that making
me uncomfortable well so we&#8217;ll pair it
up some volume here
let&#8217;s do a quick comparison here provide
audio honestly I expected to do outer if
I was gonna go through the hassle of
carrying all this around I think I want
a little more juice I think it&#8217;s a cool
concept but as it sits right now at
least the speaker unit it leaves me
wanting a little bit more next up the
mighty obviously it reminds me of mp3
players before we had smartphones the
cool thing to have was an mp3 player of
some kind it&#8217;s kind of a throwback iPod
works with Spotify Premium take all your
music with you and the ability to leave
your smartphone at home works with
Bluetooth headphones and wired
headphones thousand-plus song storage
drop resistant water-resistant
disconnect from your digital
distractions and be one with your music
for a present and more joyful light
comes in a couple different colors turn
on tune in drop out let&#8217;s move USB 2
mini Jack charge port and the headphone
jack a cliff look at this you could clip
it right here this is really bringing me
back to my ipod shuffle days all right
let&#8217;s see if this thing has any juice on
it probably not any of course there&#8217;s a
flap and update how dare you all right
so I let this thing charge overnight not
that I had to I mean
and there&#8217;s my mighty shows up right
away success and now the player connects
to Spotify zero percent of the storage
is being used you see have 96 percent
battery there guess I&#8217;ll just add a few
things to it there it is and they just
go ahead and sing such a nice simple
little player it&#8217;s a throwback getting
retro vibes here that&#8217;s kind of cool
alright so think about it last but not
least it&#8217;s called the Symphonica passive
acoustic speaker this is some old-school
stuff the amplification is strictly
coming through the design the shape of
it and the original speaker on the
smartphone oh wow whole smells delicious
it just looks cool this is so that you
can at least charge up your device when
it&#8217;s in here it&#8217;s also gonna be the
thing that holds the device there come
up through the bottom I guess this
little thumb screw I&#8217;ll screw it in
these little bands are four different
iPhones five six six plus we&#8217;re gonna
use an iPhone 10 so and I guess it just
creates a better seal let&#8217;s try to eat I
mean it&#8217;s simply not gonna compete with
proper amplification it does make the
sound a little more direct I don&#8217;t think
that&#8217;s really what this is about I mean
it just looks really cool but I think
for most people they&#8217;re gonna be better
off with a Bluetooth speaker but it will
not smell this guy
not even close</p>
</div>]]></description><link>https://live-smart.github.io/2018/02/25/3-Unique-Gadgets-You-Wouldnt-Expect-To-Exist.html</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://live-smart.github.io/2018/02/25/3-Unique-Gadgets-You-Wouldnt-Expect-To-Exist.html</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[Smart Buddy]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2018 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[3 Cool Gadgets Under $80]]></title><description><![CDATA[<iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/8QuKO5FiSDM?rel=0" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>it&#8217;s another episode of gadgets under a
price today it might be the highest
price we&#8217;ve ever done gadgets under 80
bucks as the gadgets pile up they fall
into all different price categories
let&#8217;s kick it off with this right here
this from a company called 12 South the
Fermata
it&#8217;s a headphone charging stand not just
a headphone stand but it has a built-in
micro USB cable do you have a home for
those headphones or is it a cable
factory this thing right here aims to
change that there you can see what it
looks like all set up now this thing
costs around 79 bucks
very nice unboxing experience so far
that&#8217;s aluminum whoo and that is leather
a good start the bass that was not as
satisfying as I expected it to be power
USB in here&#8217;s a USB out so this dips in
right here you slot your cable there so
it doesn&#8217;t jump out cable management
here without having it pinched by the
far edge of the base so this USB out is
to charge up any other device that seems
like the easiest thing ever there&#8217;s one
screw and one wrench micro USB cable oh
that&#8217;s nice ooh oh this is nice design
here in this guy here slots right in
there we go alright check that out
alright so if it&#8217;s not in use you can
hide this cable away well photo earbud
hook Oh even more genius can clip on
here and if you are an earbud style
listener you hook it around here the
headphones you use at your desk and the
headphones that you take out with you
look at that with the little cutout
there
these are from a previous video these
are called warehouse these are bluetooth
headphones that let you link to another
pair of bluetooth headphones so you can
share what you&#8217;re listening to enjoy
igloo why am i screaming I mean that are
yours as loud as mine oh man I&#8217;m getting
blasted hear anything oh man I just
noticed another little touch
that&#8217;s the reversible micro USB and then
hook it on unbelievable genius the
cables always where you expect it to be
from 12 South that is a cool little
product a lot of attention to detail
next up we have a wireless bluetooth
speaker from a company called I clever
it&#8217;s under 70 bucks oh look at it
apparently it&#8217;s got some bass to it
which you know that&#8217;s the thing I&#8217;m
always looking for you don&#8217;t see many
Bluetooth speakers that look like that
and then you have an LED on the back as
well this is an aluminum base on the top
is where the controls are play pause you
can answer phone calls on here this one
the sound is projecting straight at you
it&#8217;s got some decent weight to it my
base radar is starting to go you know I
mean the $3,000 $4,000 DVLA speaker I
mean that that&#8217;s not what this is this
is this is 60 something dollars okay so
let&#8217;s calibrate for that level of
analysis here like that&#8217;s one of my
favorite unbox therapy videos ever
traditional analog mini-jack input you
have what looks like a micro SD card
slot so I guess you could load music
directly onto it oh hello there I&#8217;m sure
that&#8217;s to indicate that it&#8217;s in
discovery mode line her up a podcast why
not you could bottle your enthusiasm be
an awesome pill well maybe we could talk
about so this is a mastodon that was dug
up in a pit years ago oh that&#8217;s the
great Joe Rogan there his podcast must
listen just let&#8217;s remember the price
point this is under 70 bucks
all right it&#8217;s not the loudest thing
I&#8217;ve ever had here but you already knew
that it&#8217;s not super crunchy like you
turn up the volume it doesn&#8217;t break down
there&#8217;s actually a pretty full range
there and it stays punchy and concise
even up there
on a flat surface this might be a good
way to go and a little bit of bass who&#8217;s
gonna hate on a little bit of bass this
goes back to one of my favorite videos
as well so these things here these
really cool-looking
futuristic lighters from a company
called plasmatic flameless basically
wind proof and USB rechargeable lighters
these are cool for survival-type people
they&#8217;re cool to have in a backpack if
you need to start a fire have some heat
out in the wilderness basically any
environment you&#8217;ve got the opportunity
to begin the combustion of some sort of
material it&#8217;s actually really cool now
you do need to recharge them over USB
but then the battery lasts for a really
long time you can read that for yourself
I mean it&#8217;s right there this has a nice
pattern on it and texture we have a
brushed anyway they make a bunch of
different versions it ignites to 900
degrees Fahrenheit oh my goodness can
you see that here&#8217;s the cool part if I
blow on it watch it they move around but
it won&#8217;t go out you&#8217;re not worried if it
gets a bit wet you&#8217;re certainly not
worried if it&#8217;s windy out here we go of
course we got the Don Tomas in the house
this is from the original video good old
Don Tomas like without me even going
near it
for the record I don&#8217;t smoke I&#8217;m against
it alright so the lighter does its job I
don&#8217;t want to be the guy with the twig
doing this back and forth and all I got
a spark
I think this weather I gotta spot the
family&#8217;s gonna be standing around you&#8217;ll
be lose you got that uh that plasmatic
maybe some birch bark and then I hit it
with the plasmatic who&#8217;s the king of the
castle now huh who&#8217;s the top of the food
chain now mr. plasmatic that&#8217;s who in
the past things that show up on this
show they tend to sell out on Amazon so
I&#8217;m just saying speed up if you&#8217;re
interested don&#8217;t blame me blame the show
blame Jack</p>
</div>]]></description><link>https://live-smart.github.io/2018/02/25/3-Cool-Gadgets-Under-80.html</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://live-smart.github.io/2018/02/25/3-Cool-Gadgets-Under-80.html</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[Smart Buddy]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2018 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Job Hunting Tips and Tricks]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div id="preamble">
<div class="sectionbody">
<div class="paragraph">
<p>The way we go about getting jobs has changed. Through technology and the networks that offer more intel on our prospective employers, we are better prepared than ever to find the right career path.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>The latest generation of job-seekers is also different, and not only in how it approaches the task of finding work, but in its philosophy and attitude.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Finding the right occupation is important not just for scoring a paycheck in an expensive world, but for career happiness. You, at 22, are going to work, in all likelihood, for 50 years. Make sure you love it.</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect3">
<h4 id="_the_new_job_hunters">The New Job Hunters</h4>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>There is a fearlessness about this generation. They are risk-takers, they are willing the try something new, they are willing to punch above their weight.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Younger people looking for work today also have a different outlook on failure in that they are more willing to learn from failure and do not see it as a source of shame that would forever stain their resumes. It&#8217;s generation that has come into the workforce and has been made bolder through the use of technology and information.</p>
</div>
<div id="amzn-assoc-ad-362ca55c-c25e-4b62-99e7-044b18860126"></div><script async src="//z-na.amazon-adsystem.com/widgets/onejs?MarketPlace=US&adInstanceId=362ca55c-c25e-4b62-99e7-044b18860126"></script>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Because job seekers have more access to intel – through LinkedIn, Glassdoor and other such sites – they simply know more about companies they are contemplating working for and have the power to contact employees of those firms. Because of that the interview process has become more collaborative and much more transparent.</p>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect3">
<h4 id="_is_it_time_to_find_something_new">Is It Time To Find Something New?</h4>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>One important element in a job search process is knowing, first of all, when it’s the right time to look for a new job. That means asking yourself several questions: Do you feel like you are growing in your role? Do you have the type of relationship with your manager that you want to have? And, do you see a career path laid out before you? If you have an honest conversation in those three areas, It’s pretty easy to figure out whether you’ve hit a rough patch that you can work through, or if it is time to move on.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>If you identify discontent in one or more of these areas, be aware that you might be able to rectify your situation by speaking with your manager or HR rep. If you do so and still feel unhappy, then you need to start the search process.</p>
</div>
<div class="ulist">
<ul>
<li>
<p>As it always has been, <a href="http://amzn.to/2o3iyVx">networking</a> is key. The difference now, of course, is that there are tools to do it. An internal referral or even a LinkedIn introduction can set you apart from the pack.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Social Media is important for job candidates. If you are not in a confidential search, posting to your social networks that you are looking, and what you are looking for, is an important form of networking.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Organizations still post to job sites. While <a href="http://amzn.to/2o3iyVx">LinkedIn</a>, Monster and Career Builders are still relevant, <a href="http://amzn.to/2ytviEO">Indeed.com</a> scrapes corporate web sites, so look there too. Don’t ignore, ZipRecruiter, Simply Hired and Mighty Recruiter.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Cold Calling is an option. If you have identified one or more organizations, that you believe offer the ideal work and environment, but they do not have a position posted, you can cold call.  Using publically available information, or your network for an introduction, you can send your resume and a cover letter requesting a call or visit to learn more about the company and to introduce yourself for future consideration.  Many businesses will make “opportunity hires” when they meet a great person and know they will have a need, but don’t have an open position quite yet</p>
</li>
</ul>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect3">
<h4 id="_sending_your_application">Sending Your Application</h4>
<div class="ulist">
<ul>
<li>
<p>Your resume must be flawless: spelling, grammar and accuracy still matter and can be the difference between being screened for the position and being screened out of consideration. Be sure to read <a href="http://amzn.to/2AXvGOL">How to Write a KILLER LinkedIn Profile&#8230;&#8203; And 18 Mistakes to Avoid</a>.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>The Cover Letter is not dead, but it looks different than it used to. A brief, meaningful, unique cover letter will get attention. Recruiters want to know that you actually read the job posting and believe that you are a fit, not that you are applying based on a key word search.</p>
</li>
</ul>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect3">
<h4 id="_vetting_a_job_offer">Vetting A Job Offer</h4>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>When you do receive a job offer, it’s important to understand the compensation and benefits packages that employers offer, such as…</p>
</div>
<div class="olist arabic">
<ol class="arabic">
<li>
<p>Base salary or hourly rate and the possibility for overtime pay</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Any bonus structure or signing bonus</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Tuition reimbursement and professional development costs</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Relocation assistance</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Housing, transportation, meals</p>
<div class="ulist">
<ul>
<li>
<p>On-line salary data can be useful in determining if you have received a “market rate” offer. Sites like, Glassdoor, Salry.com and PayScales can help in your research, but because they rely on candidates reporting their salary, do tend to run about 10% higher than reality.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Making a connection with the people you will be working for and with, will affect how much you like, and how well you do in your job. In the best fits, candidates report an ease in communicating and a sense of shared vision.  If your conversations with folks at the hiring company were awkward, or understanding was difficult, this may not be the right role for you.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Going back to your original list from preparing for a search, does this offer provide good work, with good people, in a good environment for you? Answer those questions for yourself.</p>
</li>
</ul>
</div>
</li>
</ol>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect3">
<h4 id="_hot_skills_and_industries">Hot Skills And Industries</h4>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Right now one of the most in-demand or beneficial skills a job applicant can have is some level of coding or understanding of software language. There’s virtually no limit to what somebody who can do some basic programming can do in the workplace because it’s not just for engineering anymore. It has invaded marketing and finance and HR—we’re all working on databases. We’ve turned into a workforce dependent upon databases, so having any kind of technical savvy there is going to enhance your career.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>For this, you might find <a href="http://amzn.to/2o4QiBB">Python Data Science Handbook: Essential Tools for Working with Data</a> useful.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Engineering, as an industry, is hot. Mechanical engineering, as a job, is in high demand. The technical demands of many engineering jobs are starting to blur the lines between white and blue collar workers.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Another space to watch is <a href="http://amzn.to/2zcM1jn">healthcare</a>, especially as it pertains to the Baby Boomer generation. Everything from home healthcare to skilled planning to housing and even financial planning for retirees or those whose careers have slowed.</p>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect3">
<h4 id="_the_future_of_job_hunting">The Future Of Job Hunting</h4>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Job seekers have never been as empowered as they are now, given the ease of research and the easy access to professional networks. This is leading to a reality in which they can, with a few simple clicks, apply for numerous jobs within a small timeframe. Since it’s so simple to apply for work, it’s harder to ascertain from simple applications who wants the job more. Going back eight or nine years, there was a natural hindrance to applying—you had to really want it. You had to know what you were talking about, you had to understand the job, you had to write the cover letter—there was an intentionality about applying that we’ve lost.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>That makes life harder for recruiters, who are forced to deal with a higher volume of applicants that can, with the press of a button, hurl reams of resume and qualification data at them. So being able to <a href="http://amzn.to/2jUefHr">stand out</a> among such competition is crucial to any job seeker.</p>
</div>
</div>]]></description><link>https://live-smart.github.io/2017/12/11/Job-Hunting-Tips-and-Tricks.html</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://live-smart.github.io/2017/12/11/Job-Hunting-Tips-and-Tricks.html</guid><category><![CDATA[job]]></category><category><![CDATA[job searching]]></category><category><![CDATA[job seeking]]></category><category><![CDATA[job hunting]]></category><category><![CDATA[finding job]]></category><category><![CDATA[recruitment]]></category><category><![CDATA[hr]]></category><category><![CDATA[career]]></category><category><![CDATA[hire]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[Smart Buddy]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2017 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[20 Biggest Lessons to be Learnt to Survive in the Corporate World]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div id="preamble">
<div class="sectionbody">
<div class="paragraph">
<p>In corporate world, sometimes no matter how well you do your job, things don’t always work out the way you want them to. Your colleagues can mistake you for competition and bring you into situations that you never wanted to be in. Here are some tips for surviving the corporate world. These may not be everything you need to know, but they’ll come in handy for dealing with your colleagues and managers.</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect2">
<h3 id="_1_it_pays_to_be_nice">1. It pays to be nice</h3>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Not to be smart. No one likes a smart-ass. It gets you nowhere.</p>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect2">
<h3 id="_2_be_nice_to_people_on_the_way_up">2. Be nice to people on the way up</h3>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Or it is real shitty on the way down</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Also read: <a href="http://amzn.to/2BlWdoT" target="_blank">Office Politics: How to Thrive in a World of Lying, Backstabbing and Dirty Tricks</a></p>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect2">
<h3 id="_3_don_t_hire_do_business_with_friends">3. Don’t hire/do business with friends</h3>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Don’t hire employees or friends. It mostly ends badly. Hire people who believe in the vision and want to partner because it makes them feel alive to be apart of something bigger than them or us. Never forget that relationships in business should be business relationships. You may have a friend or lover at work, but the relationship will end the moment the opportunity to advance in the business is placed between you and your friend or lover. By the way, keep romance outside of the workplace.</p>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect2">
<h3 id="_4_you_know_those_people_you_find_annoying">4. You know those people you find annoying?</h3>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Don’t tell anybody about those people</p>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect2">
<h3 id="_5_don_t_criticize_work_or_anyone_in_the_hallways_and_doorways">5. Don’t criticize work or anyone in the hallways and doorways</h3>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Someone is always listening …</p>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect2">
<h3 id="_6_politics_exist">6. Politics exist</h3>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Understand that politics is a fact of corporate life, and learn to deal with it. That means you take the time to understand the views of the people involved in corporate conflicts, as well as the conflicts themselves. There will be times when you have to choose between being in the right or being employed. It’s your choice. So play the game. Attend some events. Brush some shoulders</p>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect2">
<h3 id="_7_make_your_boss_look_and_feel_good">7. Make your boss look and feel good</h3>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>He’s the one that will promote you. Not your colleague. Understand what your boss regards as a priority, and help him or she accomplish it. Make sure that you document what you’ve done. Your boss needs the accomplishment, but shouldn’t get the credit for the work you’ve done.</p>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect2">
<h3 id="_8_document_your_learning_document_your_wins">8. Document your learning. Document your wins</h3>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>It’ll help as you move forward</p>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect2">
<h3 id="_9_train_another_to_do_your_job">9. Train another to do your job.</h3>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>In the months, you look to move forward. You won’t be able to get a promotion if there’s no one else to take your job.</p>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect2">
<h3 id="_10_be_reliable">10. Be reliable</h3>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Do what you say you will do. It will be remembered. Make your word your bond. Contracts are important but your word is more so. Let your yes mean yes and no mean no always. The spirit of the deal is just as important as the words of the deal. Never dishonor yourself.</p>
</div>
<div id="amzn-assoc-ad-362ca55c-c25e-4b62-99e7-044b18860126"></div><script async src="//z-na.amazon-adsystem.com/widgets/onejs?MarketPlace=US&adInstanceId=362ca55c-c25e-4b62-99e7-044b18860126"></script>
</div>
<div class="sect2">
<h3 id="_11_make_friends_with_secretaries_pa_s_and_all">11. Make friends with secretaries; PA’s and all</h3>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>They will get you out of holes and tight spots one day</p>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect2">
<h3 id="_12_don_t_look_worried">12. Don’t look worried</h3>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Ever. Leaders look ‘cool’ in the face of pressure</p>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect2">
<h3 id="_13_assume_a_cloak_of_leadership_in_tough_times">13. Assume a ‘cloak’ of leadership in tough times</h3>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Subtly. People will notice</p>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect2">
<h3 id="_14_when_emotional">14. When emotional</h3>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Take a moment. Then speak/send that email/text</p>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect2">
<h3 id="_15_there_is_no_such_thing_as_compartmentalizing_ethics">15. There is no such thing as compartmentalizing ethics.</h3>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>You can not cheat on your wife or taxes but be honest and trustworthy at the office. Fix your character flaws. We all have them. Master them or they will master you.
Make your weakness your strength.</p>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect2">
<h3 id="_16_everything_communicates">16. Everything communicates.</h3>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>How you dress, how you stand, how you speak, etc. If you want to succeed in a corporate environment, you have to communicate that you are the kind of employee that represents the corporate success story.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Also read: <a href="http://amzn.to/2k5fPX2" target="_blank">Communicating Effectively</a></p>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect2">
<h3 id="_17_don_t_confuse_your_identity">17. Don’t Confuse your Identity</h3>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>It’s a mistake to confuse your personal identity with your employment. If and when you’re sacked, you’ll be spending quite a bit of time trying to figure out who you are. Have a life outside a corporate life.</p>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect2">
<h3 id="_18_build_connections">18. Build connections</h3>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Both managers and leaders know their job with their teams is about building lots of connections. They make people feel they have a stake in common problems.</p>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect2">
<h3 id="_19_encourage_feedback">19. Encourage feedback</h3>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>It is vital that you let your team know you are interested and will listen to their concerns and ideas and contribute to solutions to any and all problems.</p>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect2">
<h3 id="_20_offer_recognition_and_always_share_success">20. Offer recognition and always share success</h3>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Focus on building team confidence by publicly recognizing their efforts and achievements. Think of it this way; anything is possible if you share the glory. Giving others a chance to claim credit is an easy, and effective, way to magnify results.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Always remember, Corporate offices are not democracies, not charities, and not therapy centers. They exist to make money, and they hired you to help them make money. That’s the deal. Keep that in mind every day, keep your emotions in check, do your job, and if you find you don’t like working there anymore, don’t complain – just keep it professional, and move on.</p>
</div>
</div>]]></description><link>https://live-smart.github.io/2017/12/02/20-Biggest-Lessons-to-be-Learnt-to-Survive-in-the-Corporate-World.html</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://live-smart.github.io/2017/12/02/20-Biggest-Lessons-to-be-Learnt-to-Survive-in-the-Corporate-World.html</guid><category><![CDATA[corporate]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[Smart Buddy]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2017 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Solution to Long Hours of Sitting]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="sect4">
<h5 id="_tl_dr">TL;DR</h5>
<div class="paragraph">
<p><a href="http://amzn.to/2BozA2p" target="_blank">Executive Office Solutions Portable Adjustable Aluminum Laptop Stand</a> is our recommended solution to the problem of modern people sitting extensive amount of hours everyday.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Our bodies are designed for regular movement, but many of us spend the bulk of their day sitting still instead. On average, a US adult spends nine to 10 hours each day sitting, which is so much inactivity that even a 30 or 60 minute workout can&#8217;t offset its effects.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Worse still, many Americans don&#8217;t fit in a workout or a long walk either, which means their bodies are virtually always in a sedentary state. It&#8217;s not that sitting is inherently dangerous. The danger is in the dose.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>While a brief period of sitting here and there is natural, long periods of sitting day-in and day-out can seriously impact your health and shorten your life.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Investigations show that when you&#8217;ve been sitting for a long period of time and then get up, a number of molecular cascades occur. For example, within 90 seconds of standing up, the muscular and cellular systems that process blood sugar, triglycerides, and cholesterol (which are mediated by insulin) are activated.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>All of these molecular effects are activated simply by carrying your own bodyweight. These cellular mechanisms are also responsible for pushing fuel into your cells and, if done regularly, will radically decrease your risk of diabetes and obesity.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>In short, at the molecular level, your body was designed to be active and on the move all day long. When you stop moving for extended periods of time, it&#8217;s like telling your body it&#8217;s time to shut down and prepare for death.</p>
</div>
<div id="amzn-assoc-ad-362ca55c-c25e-4b62-99e7-044b18860126"></div><script async src="//z-na.amazon-adsystem.com/widgets/onejs?MarketPlace=US&adInstanceId=362ca55c-c25e-4b62-99e7-044b18860126"></script>
</div>
<div class="sect3">
<h4 id="_organ_damage">Organ Damage</h4>
<div class="ulist">
<ul>
<li>
<p><strong>Heart</strong>: When you sit, blood flows slower and muscles burn less fat, which makes it easier for fatty acids to clog your heart. Research published in the Journal of the American College of Cardiology, for instance, showed that women who sit for 10 or more hours a day may have a significantly greater risk of developing heart disease than those who sit for five hours or less.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p><strong>Pancreas</strong>: Your body&#8217;s ability to respond to insulin is affected by just one day of excess sitting, which leads your pancreas to produce increased amounts of insulin, and this may lead to diabetes. Research published in Diabetologia found that those who sat for the longest periods of time were twice as likely to have diabetes or heart disease, compared to those who sat the least. Sitting for more than eight hours a day has also been associated with a 90 percent increased risk of type 2 diabetes.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p><strong>Colon Cancer</strong>: Excess sitting may increase your risk of colon, breast, and endometrial cancers. The mechanism isn&#8217;t known for certain, but it could be due to excess insulin production, which encourages cell growth, or the fact that regular movement boosts antioxidants in your body that may eliminate potentially cancer-causing free radicals. Findings presented at the 2015 Inaugural Active Working Summit also found that sitting increases:</p>
<div class="ulist">
<ul>
<li>
<p>Lung cancer by 54 percent</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Uterine cancer by 66 percent</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Colon cancer by 30 percent</p>
</li>
</ul>
</div>
</li>
</ul>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Another reason for this increased cancer risk is thought to be linked to weight gain and associated biochemical changes, such as alterations in hormones, metabolic dysfunction, leptin dysfunction, and inflammation—all of which promote cancer.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p><strong>Digestion</strong>: Sitting down after you&#8217;ve eaten causes your abdominal contents to compress, slowing down digestion. Sluggish digestion, in turn, can lead to cramping, bloating, heartburn, and constipation, as well as dysbiosis in your gastrointestinal tract, a condition caused by microbial imbalances in your body. According to Microbial Ecology in Health and Disease:</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p><em>"There is growing evidence that dysbiosis of the gut microbiota is associated with the pathogenesis of both intestinal and extra-intestinal disorders. Intestinal disorders include inflammatory bowel disease, irritable bowel syndrome (IBS), and celiac disease, while extra-intestinal disorders include allergy, asthma, metabolic syndrome, cardiovascular disease, and obesity."</em></p>
</div>
<div class="sect4">
<h5 id="_brain_damage">Brain Damage</h5>
<div class="ulist">
<ul>
<li>
<p>Your brain function slows when your body is sedentary for too long. Your brain will get less fresh blood and oxygen, which are needed to trigger the release of brain- and mood-enhancing chemicals.</p>
</li>
</ul>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect4">
<h5 id="_posture_problems">Posture Problems</h5>
<div class="ulist">
<ul>
<li>
<p>Strained Neck and Shoulders: It&#8217;s common to hold your neck and head forward while working at a computer or cradling a phone to your ear. This can lead to strains to your cervical vertebrae along with permanent imbalances, which can lead to neck strain, sore shoulders and back.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Back Problems: Sitting puts more pressure on your spine than standing, and the toll on your back health is even worse if you&#8217;re sitting hunched in front of a computer. It&#8217;s estimated that 40 percent of people with back pain have spent long hours at their computer each day. The disks in your back are meant to expand and contract as you move, which allows them to absorb blood and nutrients. When you sit, the disks are compressed and can lose flexibility over time. Sitting excessively can also increase your risk of herniated disks. Personally, after I reduced my normal 12 to 14 hours of daily sitting to under one hour, the back pain I&#8217;d struggled with for decades disappeared.</p>
</li>
</ul>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect4">
<h5 id="_muscle_degeneration">Muscle Degeneration</h5>
<div class="ulist">
<ul>
<li>
<p>Standing requires you to tense your abdominal muscles, which go unused when you sit, ultimately leading to weak abdominals.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Hip Problems: Your hips also suffer from prolonged sitting, becoming tight and limited in range of motion because they are rarely extended. In the elderly, decreased hip mobility is a leading cause of falls. Sitting also does nothing for your glutes, which may become weakened, affecting your stability and the power of your stride when walking and jumping.</p>
</li>
</ul>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect4">
<h5 id="_leg_disorders">Leg Disorders</h5>
<div class="ulist">
<ul>
<li>
<p>Varicose Veins: Sitting leads to poor circulation in your legs, which can cause swelling in your ankles, varicose veins, and blood clots known as deep vein thrombosis (DVT).</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Weak Bones: Walking, running, and engaging in other weight-bearing activities lead to stronger, denser bones. Lack of activity may cause weak bones and even osteoporosis.</p>
</li>
</ul>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect3">
<h4 id="_too_much_sitting_can_take_years_off_your_life">Too Much Sitting Can Take Years Off Your Life</h4>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>The more hours you spend sitting in a day, the shorter your lifespan may be. One study found, for instance, that reducing the average time you spend sitting down to less than three hours a day could increase your life expectancy by two years.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Another study, published in the British Journal of Sports Medicine, concluded that each hour spent watching television after the age of 25 reduces your life expectancy by nearly 22 minutes. To put this into perspective, the authors compared it to smoking – each cigarette reduces your life expectancy by about 11 minutes. All in all, the researchers found that adults who spend an average of six hours in front of the TV will reduce their life expectancy by just under 5 years, compared to someone who does not watch TV. Obesity Panacea made a good point in its report on this study:</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p><em>"These sorts of theoretical studies obviously need to be taken with a large dollop of salt (just like the recent Australian study which estimated that every hour of TV viewing shortens your life by 25 minutes). The point is simply that there is a non-negligible impact of sitting/TV viewing on mortality, and given the extremely high prevalence of these behaviors at the population level, they can have noticeable impact on the lifespan of the population as a whole."</em></p>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect3">
<h4 id="_solution">Solution</h4>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>In order for you to sit less, the solution is really simple:</p>
</div>
<a href="https://www.amazon.com/Executive-Office-Solutions-Mount-Notebook-Macbook-Light-Sitting-Black/dp/B00RQ3JQMM/ref=as_li_ss_il?s=office-products&ie=UTF8&qid=1513953933&sr=1-5&keywords=standing+desk&linkCode=li3&tag=livesmart03-20&linkId=13c275fa3f609491b983554eba92adcb" target="_blank"><img border="0" src="//ws-na.amazon-adsystem.com/widgets/q?_encoding=UTF8&ASIN=B00RQ3JQMM&Format=_SL250_&ID=AsinImage&MarketPlace=US&ServiceVersion=20070822&WS=1&tag=livesmart03-20" ></a><img src="https://ir-na.amazon-adsystem.com/e/ir?t=livesmart03-20&l=li3&o=1&a=B00RQ3JQMM" width="1" height="1" border="0" alt="" style="border:none !important; margin:0px !important;" />
<div class="paragraph">
<p><a href="http://amzn.to/2BozA2p" target="_blank">Executive Office Solutions Portable Adjustable Aluminum Laptop Stand</a> is foldable which means you can easily carry it to office. Set an alarm on your phone so that you&#8217;re reminded to switch between sit/stand positions every hour or so. You can start with standing for total of approx. 2 hours a day and gradually extend it to an optimum point for your body.</p>
</div>
</div>]]></description><link>https://live-smart.github.io/2017/12/01/Solution-to-Long-Hours-of-Sitting.html</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://live-smart.github.io/2017/12/01/Solution-to-Long-Hours-of-Sitting.html</guid><category><![CDATA[sitting]]></category><category><![CDATA[health]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[Smart Buddy]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2017 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Software Developers' Guide to Working in Open Floor Plan Office]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div id="preamble">
<div class="sectionbody">
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Offices with open floor plans have become ubiquitous in the tech industry. The idea is that eliminating physical barriers between workspaces also eliminates intellectual or interpersonal barriers to collaboration. And, of course, it’s a cost-efficient way to squeeze a lot of people into a small space.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>The problem is, programmers hate open floor plans.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>The CEO of Stack Overflow, Joel Spolsky, laid out some of the reasons programmers prefer their own space in an interview at the GeekWire technology conference. He pointed out that programming is a solitary activity, and developers don’t benefit from overhearing conversations.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>And in an open, noisy environment, that’s a difficult thing for many developers to do. At Spolsky’s three companies (Stack Overflow, Trello, and Fog Creek Software), programmers either work from home or have private offices with closing doors and natural light, he said.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Facebook’s new eight acres of open-floor office space in Silicon Valley, on the other hand, is a good example of what Spolsky thinks companies should not do.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Hundreds of developers echoed that sentiment on Reddit, in a discussion thread about Spolsky’s talk. In addition to lamenting open floor plans, they also commiserated about other distractions like unnecessary meetings and another staple of tech offices: tabletop games that generate a lot of noise.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Based on an analysis of 10,000 programming sessions recorded from 86 programmers using Eclipse and Visual Studio, and a survey of 414 programmers, we found:</p>
</div>
<div class="ulist">
<ul>
<li>
<p>A programmer takes 10-15 minutes to start editing code after resuming work from an interruption.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>When interrupted during an edit of a method, a programmer resumed work in less than a minute only 10 percent of the time.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>A programmer is likely to get just one uninterrupted two-hour session in a day.</p>
</li>
</ul>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>So how would you as a programmer overcome this open office craziness and save yourself from distractions? Here we have listed several useful tips we think might be helpful.</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect3">
<h4 id="_noise_cancelling_headphone_earphone">Noise cancelling headphone / earphone</h4>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Most of the developers probably don&#8217;t have the luxury to work from home as of yet. If you&#8217;re stuck in an office and forced to focus in a noisy surrouding, here&#8217;s to your rescue: <a href="http://amzn.to/2iVL8m4">Sony WH-1000XM2</a>, a great price-performance ratio high-end noise cancelling headphone that gives you back your inner zen in the mid of insanities.</p>
</div>
<div class="imageblock">
<div class="content">
<a class="image" href="http://amzn.to/2iVL8m4"><img src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/19504323/33706660-c5741c5c-db6f-11e7-8e29-0ee7dacbca3f.png" alt="33706660 c5741c5c db6f 11e7 8e29 0ee7dacbca3f.png"></a>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect3">
<h4 id="_quiet_corner">Quiet corner</h4>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Most of the open floor plan offices are big enough to allow some quiet corners, but most managers don&#8217;t know or don&#8217;t have the incentive to optimize the usage of it. The result being, you often see a row of noisy followed by a row of developers, followed by a row of noisy guys and so on so forth. If you&#8217;re able to negotiate with your manager so that you can work in a quieter corner of the buzz, definitely do it.</p>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect3">
<h4 id="_alternative_work_schedule">Alternative work schedule</h4>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>If possible, an alternative work schedule allows you to have minimal but enough overlap with people you&#8217;ll need to work with. You then get to focus on coding when office is almost empty.</p>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect3">
<h4 id="_work_from_home">Work from home</h4>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Better yet, if you can work from home, you naturally get away from the sources of noise. But be sure to communicate well with your managers so that they don&#8217;t think you&#8217;re doing nothing at home.</p>
</div>
</div>]]></description><link>https://live-smart.github.io/2017/12/01/Software-Developers-Guide-to-Working-in-Open-Floor-Plan-Office.html</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://live-smart.github.io/2017/12/01/Software-Developers-Guide-to-Working-in-Open-Floor-Plan-Office.html</guid><category><![CDATA[developer]]></category><category><![CDATA[programmer]]></category><category><![CDATA[software engineer]]></category><category><![CDATA[open office]]></category><category><![CDATA[open floor plan]]></category><category><![CDATA[open floor plan office]]></category><category><![CDATA[interference]]></category><category><![CDATA[interruption]]></category><category><![CDATA[earphone]]></category><category><![CDATA[headphone]]></category><category><![CDATA[work from home]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[Smart Buddy]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2017 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Christmas Gift Ideas That Make a Difference]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div id="preamble">
<div class="sectionbody">
<div class="paragraph">
<p>It&#8217;s that time of the year again. Gotta figure out what to buy for your kids, parents, significant other? Look no further, we&#8217;ve prepared a list of Christmas gift ideas that are going to <strong>make a difference</strong>.</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect2">
<h3 id="_for_parents">For Parents</h3>
<div id="natures-way-bone-formula" class="imageblock">
<div class="content">
<a class="image" href="http://amzn.to/2kyfDPu"><img src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/19504323/34067380-858b0456-e25f-11e7-9dfe-b5f8aa98e5cd.png" alt="34067380 858b0456 e25f 11e7 9dfe b5f8aa98e5cd.png"></a>
</div>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p><a href="http://amzn.to/2kyfDPu">Nature&#8217;s Way Alive!® Calcium Bone Formula Supplement</a> is not just another calcium supplement for osteoporosis. It contains vitamin C, D3 and K2 along with calcium, magnesium and more, and contains NO artificial flavoring, dairy products, preservatives, soy, wheat or yeast.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>What brings more joy than <a href="http://amzn.to/2kyfDPu">giving back stronger and healthier body to parents</a>?</p>
</div>
<hr>
</div>
<div class="sect2">
<h3 id="_for_him">For Him</h3>
<div id="echo-show" class="imageblock">
<div class="content">
<a class="image" href="http://amzn.to/2AU1iYK"><img src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/19504323/34067698-0471e2fa-e268-11e7-9ca4-7ea3ca063a70.png" alt="34067698 0471e2fa e268 11e7 9ca4 7ea3ca063a70.png"></a>
</div>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>What to buy for him? Speakers? Not bad. Smart home device? Better! Well, how about a smart speaker with screen?!;) Introducing <a href="http://amzn.to/2AU1iYK">Echo Show</a>.</p>
</div>
<div class="videoblock">
<div class="content">
<video src="https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/I/E1R7QiCtTiS.mp4" controls>
Your browser does not support the video tag.
</video>
</div>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p><a href="http://amzn.to/2AU1iYK">Echo Show</a> brings you everything you love about Alexa, and now she can show you things. Watch video flash briefings, Amazon Video content, see music lyrics, security cameras, photos, weather forecasts, to-do and shopping lists, browse and listen to Audible audiobooks, and more. All hands-free—just ask.</p>
</div>
<hr>
</div>
<div class="sect2">
<h3 id="_for_her">For Her</h3>
<div id="diamond-bracelet" class="imageblock">
<div class="content">
<a class="image" href="http://amzn.to/2BxYqjC"><img src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/19504323/34067849-e8a845b0-e26b-11e7-826c-4656ed73a877.png" alt="34067849 e8a845b0 e26b 11e7 826c 4656ed73a877.png"></a>
</div>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Maybe she would scream when she sees this, but she&#8217;d certainly scream less at you:) What woman in this world can resist beautiful artifacts such as this <a href="http://amzn.to/2BxYqjC">Sterling Silver 3 cttw Rose Cut Diamond Bracelet</a>?</p>
</div>
<div class="videoblock">
<div class="content">
<video src="https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/I/A1rmiE6iE8S.mp4" controls>
Your browser does not support the video tag.
</video>
</div>
</div>
<hr>
</div>
<div class="sect2">
<h3 id="_for_kids">For Kids</h3>
<div id="coc-figure-pack" class="imageblock">
<div class="content">
<a class="image" href="http://amzn.to/2CEx35e"><img src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/19504323/34067638-80499ba4-e266-11e7-94d9-ca4ea02f71c0.png" alt="34067638 80499ba4 e266 11e7 94d9 ca4ea02f71c0.png"></a>
</div>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>You know of kids who don&#8217;t play CoC / Clash Royale? This <a href="http://amzn.to/2CEx35e">figure pack of 5</a> is gonna make their Christmas for sure.</p>
</div>
<hr>
</div>
<div class="sect2">
<h3 id="_for_yourself">For Yourself</h3>
<div id="nuskin-pharmanex-lifepak" class="imageblock">
<div class="content">
<a class="image" href="http://amzn.to/2zfFnZy"><img src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/19504323/34067594-0b20bd7c-e265-11e7-96c3-a7cad9b67995.png" alt="34067594 0b20bd7c e265 11e7 96c3 a7cad9b67995.png"></a>
</div>
</div>
<div id="nuskin-pharmanex-lifepak1" class="paragraph">
<p>Family is no family without you. You&#8217;re at least half of the cornerstones that support it. A wealthy family can&#8217;t do without a healthy you.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p><a href="http://amzn.to/2zfFnZy">NuSkin Pharmanex LifePak</a> is a comprehensive dietary supplement with important antioxidants, vitamins, minerals, and phytonutrients to support anti-aging benefits. It supplies a comprehensive blend of nutrients to support a healthy cardiovascular system and provides comprehensive bone nutrition support. It also promotes healthy immune function and supports normal blood sugar metabolism.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p><a href="http://amzn.to/2zfFnZy">Treat yourself better</a> from now on.</p>
</div>
<div class="sect3">
<h4 id="_merry_christmas">Merry Christmas!</h4>

</div>
</div>]]></description><link>https://live-smart.github.io/2017/12/01/Christmas-Gift-Ideas-That-Make-a-Difference.html</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://live-smart.github.io/2017/12/01/Christmas-Gift-Ideas-That-Make-a-Difference.html</guid><category><![CDATA[christmas]]></category><category><![CDATA[gift]]></category><category><![CDATA[echo]]></category><category><![CDATA[lifepak]]></category><category><![CDATA[bone formula]]></category><category><![CDATA[clash of clans]]></category><category><![CDATA[clash royale]]></category><category><![CDATA[bracelet]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[Smart Buddy]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2017 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Diet for Programmers / Software Engineers / Hackers / Geeks]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="paragraph">
<p>Are you a software developer / engineer who, like virtually any other out there has a "beer belly" to deal with? Is your career surging while your health is spiraling down? Has your doctor told you to cut calories in your diet and do more exercises?</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Well, it&#8217;d probably be hard for you to squeeze 15 minutes out everyday to do exercises. Those drinking sessions are probably hard to avoid too. Is there a solid way to fix all these, flatten the belly and make the life a bit easier and healthier?</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p><a href="http://amzn.to/2AVVPPY">Balanced Greens Organic Vegan Protein Powder</a> to the rescue.</p>
</div>
<div class="imageblock">
<div class="content">
<a class="image" href="http://amzn.to/2AVVPPY"><img src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/19504323/33814649-99fd13e0-de66-11e7-814b-54b73d4a35af.png" alt="33814649 99fd13e0 de66 11e7 814b 54b73d4a35af.png"></a>
</div>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Being completely organic, it&#8217;s an all-in-one probiotics, antioxidants, fiber and digestive enzymes meal replacement shake which targets to alkalize, energize and detox your body. No bother with seeking and preparing ingredients yourself anymore. They&#8217;re all in there.</p>
</div>
<div class="imageblock">
<div class="content">
<a class="image" href="http://amzn.to/2AVVPPY"><img src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/19504323/33814651-9f56b2ce-de66-11e7-8816-ea0ac79ce7ab.png" alt="33814651 9f56b2ce de66 11e7 8816 ea0ac79ce7ab.png"></a>
</div>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p><strong>Fiber</strong> for example, is one of weight loss&#8217;s little secrets. The main structural component of plants, fiber can&#8217;t be digested by the human body. Its primary purpose is to add bulk to the contents of your stomach and digestive tract, which helps move things along and keeps you regular. As a bonus, the extra bulk in your belly helps fill you up and keep you feeling full so you can limit your calorie intake. Having a fiber-rich shake as a snack or meal replacement each day just might be what you need to shed those extra pounds. Fiber-rich foods, such as fruits, vegetables and whole grains, tend to be healthy and low in energy density, or calories per gram. Eating a lot of low-energy-dense foods helps fill you up on fewer calories so you can control your calorie intake to lose weight. According to a review published in "Nutrition" in March 2005, dietary fiber intake is inversely associated with body weight; people who eat more fiber tend to weigh less and have less body fat.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Replacing one meal a day with a <a href="http://amzn.to/2AVVPPY">nutritious, high-fiber shake</a> can help you create the calorie deficit required for weight loss. To lose 1 to 2 pounds per week, which is considered a safe and healthy rate of weight loss, you need to trim 500 to 1,000 calories from your daily diet. If you normally go out for lunch with coworkers and take in 800 calories or more, skipping the lunch outing and whipping up a fiber-rich shake in the kitchen at your office can save you 500 calories. That one change is enough to lose 4 pounds in a month.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Programmers, software engineers, hackers, geeks, ready to buff up your overall energy and health? <a href="http://amzn.to/2AVVPPY">Try it</a> now:)</p>
</div>]]></description><link>https://live-smart.github.io/2017/11/30/Best-Diet-for-Programmers-Software-Engineers-Hackers-Geeks.html</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://live-smart.github.io/2017/11/30/Best-Diet-for-Programmers-Software-Engineers-Hackers-Geeks.html</guid><category><![CDATA[diet]]></category><category><![CDATA[programmers]]></category><category><![CDATA[software engineers]]></category><category><![CDATA[hackers]]></category><category><![CDATA[geeks]]></category><category><![CDATA[health]]></category><category><![CDATA[shake]]></category><category><![CDATA[fibre]]></category><category><![CDATA[fiber]]></category><category><![CDATA[yoghurt]]></category><category><![CDATA[weight loss]]></category><category><![CDATA[probiotics]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[Smart Buddy]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2017 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Some Great Books on Investment]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div id="preamble">
<div class="sectionbody">
<div class="paragraph">
<p>It&#8217;s imperative for young adults and professionals to start investing early. One of the main reasons for doing so is to obtain the power of compound interest; by holding long-term investments, one can allow his or her assets to generate more returns. Investing just a few years earlier could translate into tens of thousands, if not hundreds of thousands, of additional funds for your retirement nest egg.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>But while it is important to invest early, it is also important to invest wisely. These five classic investing books can provide indispensable business and finance insights for young investors.</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect2">
<h3 id="__a_href_http_amzn_to_2av1vrp_rich_dad_poor_dad_2000_a_by_robert_kiyosaki"><a href="http://amzn.to/2Av1Vrp">"Rich Dad, Poor Dad" (2000)</a> by Robert Kiyosaki</h3>
<div class="imageblock">
<div class="content">
<a class="image" href="http://amzn.to/2Av1Vrp"><img src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/19504323/33874370-7a2599a4-df59-11e7-86f1-453de69da698.png" alt="33874370 7a2599a4 df59 11e7 86f1 453de69da698.png"></a>
</div>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>This classic is a must-read for young investors. Kiyosaki&#8217;s view is that the poor and middle class work for money, but the rich work to learn. He stresses the importance of financial literacy, and presents financial independence as the ultimate goal, and a way to avoid the rat race of corporate America. The author points out that while accounting is important to learn, it can also be misleading. Banks label a house as an asset for the individual, but because of the required payments to keep it, it can really be a liability in terms of cash flow. Real assets add cash flow to your wallet.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Kiyosaki advocates investments that produce periodic cash flow for the investor while providing upside in terms of equity value. Real estate investments and stocks that provide dividends are viewed favorably. The author advises that America&#8217;s educational system is designed to keep people working hard for the rest of their lives, and that the school system does a poor job of teaching people to create enough wealth so they won&#8217;t have to work anymore. Kiyosaki also highlights the importance of tax planning.</p>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect2">
<h3 id="__a_href_http_amzn_to_2ayfwba_the_essays_of_warren_buffett_lessons_for_corporate_america_1997_a_by_warren_buffett"><a href="http://amzn.to/2AYFWbA">"The Essays of Warren Buffett: Lessons For Corporate America" (1997)</a> by Warren Buffett</h3>
<div class="imageblock">
<div class="content">
<a class="image" href="http://amzn.to/2AYFWbA"><img src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/19504323/33874451-d45575ca-df59-11e7-82a2-278ecb536ae8.png" alt="33874451 d45575ca df59 11e7 82a2 278ecb536ae8.png"></a>
</div>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>In his essays, Warren Buffett—widely considered to be modern history&#8217;s most successful investor—provides his views on a variety of topics important to corporate America and shareholders. Young investors can get a glimpse of the interface between a company&#8217;s management and its shareholders, as well as the thought processes involved in enhancing a company&#8217;s enterprise value.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Buffett&#8217;s essays include discussions on corporate governance, finance, investing, alternatives to common stock, mergers and acquisitions, accounting and valuation, accounting policy, and tax matters. Buffett outlines his basic business principles, and as the steward of Berkshire Hathaway Inc. (BRK-A
), informs the shareholders of the company that their mutual interests are aligned. He has a philosophy of bringing in talented managers at portfolio companies and leaving them alone. He advocates purchasing shares of businesses at times when these stocks are trading at a discount from their inherent value. He opposes following investing trends.</p>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect2">
<h3 id="__a_href_http_amzn_to_2au8y3c_beating_the_street_1994_a_by_peter_lynch"><a href="http://amzn.to/2Au8Y3C">"Beating the Street" (1994)</a> by Peter Lynch</h3>
<div class="imageblock">
<div class="content">
<a class="image" href="http://amzn.to/2Au8Y3C"><img src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/19504323/33874512-044dd2d6-df5a-11e7-9a03-8ee3740e57ec.png" alt="33874512 044dd2d6 df5a 11e7 9a03 8ee3740e57ec.png"></a>
</div>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Peter Lynch is one of the most successful stock market investors and hedge fund managers of the 20th century. He started out as an intern at Fidelity Investments in the mid 1960s. Nearly 11 years later, he was tasked to manage the Magellan Fund, which at the time had close to $18 million in assets. By 1990, the fund had grown to a whopping $18 billion in assets with nearly 1,000 stock positions. During this time, the fund boasted average returns of more than 29% per year.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>"Beating The Street" allows the reader to peek into Lynch&#8217;s mind and thought processes in terms of deciding whether to buy or sell a stock. Lynch believes that an individual investor could exploit market opportunities better than Wall Street, and encourages investors to invest in what they know.</p>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect2">
<h3 id="__a_href_http_amzn_to_2kwffqb_the_intelligent_investor_1949_a_by_benjamin_graham"><a href="http://amzn.to/2kWFFQb">"The Intelligent Investor" (1949)</a> by Benjamin Graham</h3>
<div class="imageblock">
<div class="content">
<a class="image" href="http://amzn.to/2kWFFQb"><img src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/19504323/33874540-23efa4a2-df5a-11e7-84c2-e08ebc4353fa.png" alt="33874540 23efa4a2 df5a 11e7 84c2 e08ebc4353fa.png"></a>
</div>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>This book was written in 1949 and has been hailed by Warren Buffett as the best investing book ever written. Benjamin Graham is considered the "father of value investing." This paradigm advocates the purchase of stocks that appear under-priced relative to their inherent value, which is determined through fundamental analysis.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Graham delves into the history of the stock market, and informs the reader on conducting fundamental analysis on a stock. He discusses various ways of managing your portfolio including both a positive and defensive approach. He then compares the stocks of several companies to illustrate his points.</p>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect2">
<h3 id="__a_href_http_amzn_to_2yzumm1_think_and_grow_rich_1937_a_by_napoleon_hill"><a href="http://amzn.to/2yZumM1">"Think and Grow Rich" (1937)</a> by Napoleon Hill</h3>
<div class="imageblock">
<div class="content">
<a class="image" href="http://amzn.to/2yZumM1"><img src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/19504323/33874699-9dee87a0-df5a-11e7-8b1c-d58cc3629e0b.png" alt="33874699 9dee87a0 df5a 11e7 8b1c d58cc3629e0b.png"></a>
</div>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>"Think and Grow Rich" was written during the Great Depression, and has since sold more than 30 million copies worldwide. Hill conducted extensive research based on his associations with wealthy individuals during his lifetime. At the suggestion of Andrew Carnegie, Hill published 13 principles for success and personal achievement from his observations and research. These include desire, faith, specialized knowledge, organized planning, persistence and the "sixth sense." Hill also believed in brainstorming with like-minded people, whose efforts can create synergistic energy.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>This book conveys valuable insights into the psychology of success and abundance, and should be considered a priority read given the current age&#8217;s emphasis on shock-value entertainment and negative news.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>The best investors did not emerge overnight, but honed their skills through years of thought, research and practice. When you are done with these books, here are several more to add to your reading list.</p>
</div>
</div>]]></description><link>https://live-smart.github.io/2017/11/28/Some-Great-Books-on-Investment.html</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://live-smart.github.io/2017/11/28/Some-Great-Books-on-Investment.html</guid><category><![CDATA[investment]]></category><category><![CDATA[make money]]></category><category><![CDATA[revenue]]></category><category><![CDATA[income]]></category><category><![CDATA[profit]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[Smart Buddy]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2017 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Sony WH-1000XM2 Noise Cancelling Wireless Headphone]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="sect2">
<h3 id="_what_are_the_sony_wh_1000xm2">What are the Sony WH-1000XM2?</h3>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>In 2016, the Trusted Reviews award for Best Headphones went to the Sony MDR-1000X, excellent wireless and noise-cancelling headphones with an intelligent set of features. The <a href="http://amzn.to/2iVL8m4">Sony WH-1000XM2</a> are their successor, and they’re a little better in almost every way.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>The market is tougher now, and Sony faces fierce competition from the <a href="http://amzn.to/2z5oZKX">Bose QuietComfort 35 II</a> and <a href="http://amzn.to/2Azwhco">B&amp;W PX</a>. But the new <a href="http://amzn.to/2iVL8m4">Sony WH-1000XM2</a> get so many things right it’s hard to fault them. They sound great, the noise cancellation is effective, and most of the features are genuinely useful.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>If you’re looking for an everyday pair of headphones, these are hard to beat.</p>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect2">
<h3 id="_design">Design</h3>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>The <a href="http://amzn.to/2nSPJLj">Sony MDR-1000X</a> had an excellent design that didn’t need fixing, so Sony has basically left it alone. That’s fine, since it meant the company could spare some resources towards expanding the <a href="http://amzn.to/2iVL8m4">WH-1000XM2</a> range – check out the <a href="http://amzn.to/2iZKcxl">Sony WF-1000X</a> wireless earbuds.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Anyway, the <a href="http://amzn.to/2iVL8m4">Sony WH-1000XM2</a> are more of a facelift than a makeover – there are a few minor improvements over the original, but unless you’re really looking for them you probably won’t notice.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>They still look very smart, with the same streamlined silhouette and hardly any branding. The body is mainly plastic, with polished metal in the headband and good quality synthetic leather at the ears.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>The paintjob is a little different: the beige version is now closer to champagne gold, while the black version is more gunmetal greyish blue. This adds a little visual flair, but the overall effect is no less subtle. If you want something with an executive vibe, the <a href="http://amzn.to/2iVL8m4">Sony WH-1000XM2</a> will do nicely.</p>
</div>
<div class="imageblock">
<div class="content">
<a class="image" href="http://amzn.to/2japefG"><img src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/19504323/33707661-1abce4d4-db73-11e7-9563-da24f9f08f1c.png" alt="33707661 1abce4d4 db73 11e7 9563 da24f9f08f1c.png"></a>
</div>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>The synthetic leather on the outside of the ear cups has been swapped for a more tactile alternative. It’s less smooth to the touch – some might say it’s more plasticky – but I feel it’s thicker and tougher. I welcome this change, because the smooth finish of the original always seemed at risk of scratching. Now I feel a little less bad throwing them straight into my bag without first using the protective carry case.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>What hasn’t changed is the polyurethane foam stuffed into the headband and ear pads. They’re as squishy as ever, and the <a href="http://amzn.to/2iVL8m4">Sony WH-1000XM2</a> are as comfortable as their predecessors. Clamp force is just right; they hold the sides of your head but never squeeze. As before, the headband expands with satisfying clicks. The earcups can fold inwards on hinges, as well as swivel flat.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>The buttons have been streamlined. Power/pairing remains where it is, but noise cancelling and ambient sound adjustment have been merged into one. That makes it a little harder to press the wrong thing, which might sound minor, but there’s value in being able to just get on with your listening.</p>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect2">
<h3 id="_features">Features</h3>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>The improvements to the features list is a lot less subtle. There have been quite a lot of tweaks and additions.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>The Bluetooth has been upgraded. The <a href="http://amzn.to/2iVL8m4">Sony WH-1000XM2</a> are compatible with aptX HD, a higher quality Bluetooth format that can handle hi-res audio up to 24bit/48kHz. LDAC is also included, and it can handle 24bit/96kHz, but it’s a proprietary Sony format, limited to Sony devices. The left ear has an NFC chip for quicker Bluetooth pairing.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>The touch-sensitive control pad on the right ear cup has been tightened up, so your inputs feel more accurate and responsive.The Quick Attention mode, where you hold your palm to the right ear to mute, remains unchanged.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>The Ambient Sound feature is smarter. It still allows audio passthrough so you can be more aware of the outside world, but now it’s adaptive. The strength of noise cancellation will vary according to what you’re doing – sitting around, walking around, riding in vehicles or running for the bus.</p>
</div>
<div class="imageblock">
<div class="content">
<a class="image" href="http://amzn.to/2japefG"><img src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/19504323/33707728-5f5b2c22-db73-11e7-9974-1a5480a98fb0.png" alt="33707728 5f5b2c22 db73 11e7 9974 1a5480a98fb0.png"></a>
</div>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>The Optimizer feature has also been improved. It still scans the side of your head to measure how good the seal is, factoring in sunglasses or big hair and adjusting the sound accordingly, but now it uses a pressure sensor too.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Why? Sony says changes in atmospheric pressure can affect the way the drivers and noise-cancelling microphones work. The 1000XM2 measure the barometric pressure in your immediate surroundings, and then compensates the sound accordingly. The idea is that you should get the best noise cancellation the headphones can offer, no matter if you’re in a train or 35,000 feet in the air.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>In the time I had to test the Sony WH-1000XM2, I didn’t have any flights booked, so I can’t comment on the effectiveness of the pressure sensor. But the Optimizer feature definitely works, and I find myself re-calibrating the sound when I wear glasses.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>You can now tinker with the headphones with a mobile app. This lets you adjust the severity of the noise cancellation, or disable it entirely. You can also choose to prioritise connection stability over sound quality, or vice versa. That’s genuinely handy if you’re in a busy office or station and other people’s wireless signal interferes.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Less useful are the virtual positioning and virtual surround modes. The first lets you move the soundstage in front or around you; the second attempts to replicate the acoustics of spaces such as ‘concert hall’ or ‘arena’. I wouldn’t bother with these as they just make the music sound worse. If you want really want to mess with your sound quality, I’d just play with the EQ settings.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>There’s also the DSEE (Digital Sound Enhancement Engine) processing, which claims to upscale compressed audio. This was on all the time in the previous version, but now you have the option to turn it off. I’d leave it on as it actually helps a little.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>It would be reasonable to assume all these features sap battery life, but there is actually more juice than ever. The original 1000X lasted up to 20 hours, but the <a href="http://amzn.to/2iVL8m4">Sony WH-1000XM2</a> goes up to 30 hours (wireless) or 40 hours (wired).</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>There’s even a quick charge feature – 10 minutes at the mains will give you 70 minutes’ play time. A few headphone manufacturers have switched over to USB-C for power, but Sony has stuck with the ubiquitous microUSB.</p>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect2">
<h3 id="_performance">Performance</h3>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>When it comes to noise cancellation, the <a href="http://amzn.to/2iVL8m4">Sony WH-1000XM2</a> are some of the best you can buy. I put them through a varied assault course including excited cafe chatter, rattling train carriages, roadworks with pneumatic drills and speakers blasting plane engine noises – the <a href="http://amzn.to/2iVL8m4">WH-1000XM2</a> dialled all that down to a whisper.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>They’re not quite as deadly silent as the <a href="http://amzn.to/2z5oZKX">Bose QuietComfort 35 II</a>, but it’s not a huge difference, and they’re more effective than the <a href="http://amzn.to/2Azwhco">B&amp;W PX</a>. I could (and did) fall asleep listening to these headphones on a train.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>It’s not just the effective noise cancellation that impresses me – it’s the smart element that Sony has introduced. The headphone app works with the accelerometers in your phone to determine whether you’re at rest, in motion or in transit – and the levels of noise cancellation really do change accordingly.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>In ‘Staying’ mode, the headphones let some voices in so I could still tell if a colleagues wanted my attention. In ‘Walking’ mode, they let in more ambient noise so I could be aware of approaching traffic. As soon as I got onto a train, Transport mode kicked in and noise cancellation was dialled up to maximum. You can turn this off, but I love it.</p>
</div>
<div class="imageblock">
<div class="content">
<a class="image" href="http://amzn.to/2japefG"><img src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/19504323/33708007-36ebc052-db74-11e7-866e-3dcaebd9a4f4.png" alt="33708007 36ebc052 db74 11e7 866e 3dcaebd9a4f4.png"></a>
</div>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>As for audio performance, the <a href="http://amzn.to/2iVL8m4">WH-1000XM2</a> have many of the traits I admired so much about the original. They’re a hugely entertaining listen, thanks to a combination of hard-hitting dynamism, boundless energy and impressive rhythmic precision.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>That agility partly comes down to its impressive articulation and neutral tonal balance. No part of the frequency range feels exaggerated, and everything is nicely defined. There’s no flab to the bass, the midrange is direct and succinct, and the treble is clean, free of sibilance. It’s a very tidy presentation.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Compared to the original MDR-1000X, I found the <a href="http://amzn.to/2iVL8m4">WH-1000XM2</a> to be a little clearer and more hard-hitting. But the audio components are the same, so I’m going to put this down to the fact that I was using aptX HD compatible music devices (an LG G6 and Astell &amp; Kern AK70). In wired mode, there was no discernable difference.</p>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect2">
<h3 id="_why_buy_the_a_href_http_amzn_to_2ivl8m4_sony_wh_1000xm2_a">Why buy the <a href="http://amzn.to/2iVL8m4">Sony WH-1000XM2</a>?</h3>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>The <a href="http://amzn.to/2iVL8m4">Sony WH-1000XM2</a> have improved on their predecessors in nearly every way. The physical design has been tweaked for the better, the audio performance is stronger, and the noise cancellation is smarter.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>So the competition is tougher this year, but that’s not a problem for Sony. The <a href="http://amzn.to/2z5oZKX">Bose QuietComfort 35 II</a> offer more effective noise cancellation, but they’re not as musically talented. The <a href="http://amzn.to/2Azwhco">B&amp;W PX</a> are the best-sounding of the lot, but they’re not as smart or as good at noise-cancelling.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Sony, meanwhile, have excellent all-rounders that excel in every department.</p>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect2">
<h3 id="_verdict">Verdict</h3>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>The best just got better. <a href="http://amzn.to/2iVL8m4">Try it out</a> for yourself now.</p>
</div>
</div>]]></description><link>https://live-smart.github.io/2017/11/19/Sony-WH-1000X-M-Noise-Cancelling-Wireless-Headphone.html</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://live-smart.github.io/2017/11/19/Sony-WH-1000X-M-Noise-Cancelling-Wireless-Headphone.html</guid><category><![CDATA[noise-cancelling]]></category><category><![CDATA[earphone]]></category><category><![CDATA[sony]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[Smart Buddy]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2017 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Learn Programming the Right Way]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div id="preamble">
<div class="sectionbody">
<div class="paragraph">
<p>TL;DR, here are the books that will pave your way to a becoming a successful programmer. Be sure to read them in the right order.</p>
</div>
<div class="olist arabic">
<ol class="arabic">
<li>
<p><a href="http://amzn.to/2AD6OPc">Inside the Machine: An Illustrated Introduction to Microprocessors and Computer Architecture</a></p>
</li>
<li>
<p><a href="http://amzn.to/2jTiQto">Modern X86 Assembly Language Programming: 32-bit, 64-bit, SSE, and AVX</a></p>
</li>
<li>
<p><a href="http://amzn.to/2j3pxZf">C Programming Language</a></p>
</li>
</ol>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Once you go through above books, you&#8217;ll be ready for a developer career in any direction.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>A lot of us who&#8217;re just getting started in programming often are misled into starting with reading a book on one of the programming languages, such as C. This is unfortunately terribly wrong for beginners in my opinion. It&#8217;s like for a baby to learn to walk before she can crawl.</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect3">
<h4 id="_crawl_stage">Crawl Stage</h4>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Programming language like C are called high-level languages, despite there are much higher level languages out there. During the Crawl Stage it&#8217;s important to acknowledge that you should kick off with something lower than a high-level language.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>A first step I would recommend is to learn how a computer works. This is nothing to do with software yet. It&#8217;s the hardware level of things, such as CPU, buses, memory that determine how software is run. Programming without knowledge at this level is like driving a car without knowing how an engine works - You wouldn&#8217;t get very far.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p><a href="http://amzn.to/2AD6OPc">Inside the Machine: An Illustrated Introduction to Microprocessors and Computer Architecture</a> is exactly a book for that.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Once you are familiar with how computers work under the hood, it&#8217;s time to learn how to command them to do stuff for you. But no rush yet. You surely can command them with any programming language, but do start with Assembly, which is a machine level language that directly works with CPU, registers, memory, etc. All languages are eventually compiled to machine code, but Assembly is the lowest-level possible human readable language you can access.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p><a href="http://amzn.to/2jTiQto">Modern X86 Assembly Language Programming: 32-bit, 64-bit, SSE, and AVX</a> would be great book on that.</p>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect3">
<h4 id="_walk_stage">Walk Stage</h4>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Virtually no one uses Assembly language to code real world applications. It&#8217;s not as wieldy as we desire. High-level languages such as C, Java help abstract away many details and encapsulate what can be blocks or pages of code in Assembly within much more concise and human-readable code structure.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p><a href="http://amzn.to/2j3pxZf">C Programming Language</a> is a book I would recommend even if you don&#8217;t need it in your job. It&#8217;s got a lot of what you need to know about a high-level language such as basic logic structures, arithmetic operations, function definitions, etc. You&#8217;ll find it much smoother with other languages once you grasp this one.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>I&#8217;ll later write about higher-level languages and programming paradigms. Stay tuned.</p>
</div>
<div class="sect5">
<h6 id="__books_recommended_in_this_post">* Books recommended in This Post</h6>
<div class="olist arabic">
<ol class="arabic">
<li>
<p><a href="http://amzn.to/2AD6OPc">Inside the Machine: An Illustrated Introduction to Microprocessors and Computer Architecture</a></p>
</li>
<li>
<p><a href="http://amzn.to/2jTiQto">Modern X86 Assembly Language Programming: 32-bit, 64-bit, SSE, and AVX</a></p>
</li>
<li>
<p><a href="http://amzn.to/2j3pxZf">C Programming Language</a></p>
</li>
</ol>
</div>
</div>
</div>]]></description><link>https://live-smart.github.io/2017/11/11/Learn-Programming-the-Right-Way.html</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://live-smart.github.io/2017/11/11/Learn-Programming-the-Right-Way.html</guid><category><![CDATA[programming]]></category><category><![CDATA[development]]></category><category><![CDATA[assembly]]></category><category><![CDATA[computer architecture]]></category><category><![CDATA[c]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[Smart Buddy]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2017 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[102 Tips To Improve Your Relationship]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="paragraph">
<p>Being part of a couple is hard, but the best relationship tips are really all about maintenance. You’ve got to keep things fresh, find time for each other, and come up with ways to navigate the tricky ups and downs every partnership faces. That all sounds a lot easier than it really is, so we’ve come up with 101 ways to make your relationship even better.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>From how to deal with jealousy to how to get over a potentially deadly lull, we’ve got 101 relationship tips that you can start implementing right now.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Also Read: <a href="http://amzn.to/2CCdNo4" target="_blank">How to Be an Adult in Relationships: The Five Keys to Mindful Loving</a></p>
</div>
<div class="olist arabic">
<ol class="arabic">
<li>
<p>Listen.
It might sound obvious, but when you really allow yourself to listen—and ask questions about—what your partner says, it not only leads to better conversations, but also better communication.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Take a few days apart.
Missing each other is a great way to reconnect. Try grabbing some girlfriends for an overnight or a weekend getaway every few months.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Find a support team.
Have a handful of great friends or family members you can call so your significant other doesn’t have to hear every small grievance going on your life.
MORE: 9 Things Every Woman Deserves in a Relationship</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Put away your phones.
One of the biggest relationship tips is to give your undivided attention when your partner is speaking. It’s is one of the most important things you can do.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Volunteer together.
Giving back is a great way to keep perspective of how great your relationship is, and how lucky you both are.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Create a checklist.
Jot down new and fun things you want to accomplish for a day as a duo.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Talk to couples over 65 years old.
Get relationship tips from them, and see what you can take away to apply to your relationship.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Stop and appreciate all that your relationship is this very second.
Stop living for what it can be.  This person is choosing to be in your life every day, not every day in the future.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Revisit the questions you asked in the beginning.
What are you hoping to accomplish in the next year? What are you scared of? These answers change, so we need to keep asking these questions.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Find 10 things you really love about them and tell them.
Guys need confidence boosters, too!</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Stop nagging.
Seriously, stop. Take a step back and figure out the big things about your partner that truly bother you, and approach them from a place of concern and support instead of nitpicking for sport. That’ll get you nowhere.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Get over needing to be right.
Learning to say “I was wrong” is a skill worth learning.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Take care of yourself.
No relationship can be successful if you don’t feel good about yourself, both inside and out.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Know what you need and then ask for it.
You’re dating a human, not a magical psychic.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Take a class.
It’s proven that couples who learn together connect deeper. Find some common ground (cooking? art? science?) and go from there.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Stop complicating things that aren’t complicated enough.
Don’t pull a Carrie Bradshaw during the Aiden years: If you bemoan the fact that your relationship is going too well, you might need to revisit why you’re constantly seeking out drama.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Assume that if something was said that hurt your feelings, it wasn’t intended that way.
Why would they want to upset you or hurt you? Give your partner the benefit of the doubt, but if it’s really bothering you, don’t be afraid to bring it up.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Write notes.
Whether you have study hall together or live together, handwritten notes are personal touches in today’s highly digital world.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Pitch in.
Help each other with chores and other necessary, if banal, activities — cooking, cleaning, re-organizing, etc. Not doing them if you live together can create tension, and always doing them can create unfair expectations. Act as team of equals.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Disconnect.
Step away from the laptop during quality time. Everything on the Internet will still be there later.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Allow things to be what they are.
Sometimes bad days and bad moods happen. Don’t go crazy trying to make everything better. Just be supportive and loving, because just being there at the end of a bad day can make it better for both of you.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Create mini-traditions.
Creating small rituals can really help hold up a couple because they become “your thing.” Whether it’s a fancy night out during the holiday season, or watching a certain show every week, these are things that’ll give you both something to look forward to, and it’ll bring you closer together.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Be an open book.
They can either deal with it or they can’t, but if you can’t be your most honest self with this person, it’ll come out eventually.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Compliment, and often.
You’re there to make each other feel like your best selves, so let the genuine praise flow freely. Like his outfit? Tell him! Like her hair today? Let her know!</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Make promises that you really can keep.
Say things that you want to follow through with out loud. It’ll make you work harder to make them happen. Having—and setting—levels of reasonable expectations for your relationship is a healthy way to keep it strong.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Acknowledge positive actions.
When you and your partner see positive actions, solutions, or behavior in one another, acknowledge it and remind each other to keep it up.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Establish genuine connections with the other’s friends and family.
Hang out together with both of your friends and family. This is the stuff that makes the world go ’round, people!</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Pay attention to the tiny things that bother your partner, and if it’s painless for you, work to change them.
We’re not talking changing your laugh or your style, but if you know that your partner really hates it when you leave the kitchen counter cluttered, try to make a point of clearing it off before he gets home. It’s an easy enough thing to do and it makes their day better, so why not?</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Never, never forget to ask about the other person’s day.
It’s such an easy slight to avoid!</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Only one person gets to have the bad day.
If your partner’s day sucked and yours was just “eh,” let them have the pity (and the control of the remote, and the choice of take-out). If it’s you, announce it early and let them know you need the support. If it’s a toss-up, trade stories about why your days were so awful and you’ll end up laughing while trying to figure out who wins.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Small gifts go a long way.
Bringing home a pack of their favorite candy/magazine/book by a favorite author never gets old.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Graham Parsons has a song lyric that says “I just want to hold you, I don’t want to hold you down.”
Let that be your motto when you’re giving your partner advice.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Log onto Instagram and like all their photos.
Just because.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Plan a date where you revisit the spot you went on your first date.
Remember all the amazing things that brought you from then to now.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Go on a walk together somewhere beautiful.
And don’t forget to turn off your cell phones.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Surprise them with dinner.
One unexpected night, surprise your partner with a home-cooked meal, and a nicely-set table.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Review your top five favorite funny things your partner has done.
Because your partner is funny! That’s part of why you like them.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Go to a yoga class together.
Or other exercise class together. Your body and relationship will thank you!</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Go on a road trip, even if you’re not going anywhere far.
It’s nice to get out of town sometimes.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Pick up a six-pack of toilet paper or (even better) a six-pack of beer.
Without even being asked.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Keep the surprises coming.
Think of your relationship as a creative challenge. To keep the romance fresh, come up with new date ideas, new sex positions, and new ways to demonstrate your love.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Plan small outings.
Whether its brunch this weekend, or a trip to a new neighborhood.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Make out.
Kissing is something that is often set to the side the longer a couple has been together. Out of blue one day, initiate a high-school style make-out session.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Let it go.
Don’t hold onto that thing your lover said or did six months ago and bring it up each time you get mad at him. Do both of you a favor and let it go</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Don’t interrupt.
Even if what you think your significant other is saying is uninteresting, don’t bulldoze over his or her words. Being able to listen to each other—even when the details are mundane—is important.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Say thanks.
Let him know that you notice the little things he does by saying thank you for routine tasks like walking the dog or picking up groceries.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Cook a meal together.
Come up with a menu, shop, and prepare the food together.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Have fun with hypotheticals.
Conversation can become routine. Break from the ordinary and have a silly dinner conversation made entirely of imaginary situations—for example, “If you were on an island and could only bring five movies, which movies would you bring?</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Keep a couple’s journal.
Write down your desires and fantasies and leave them out for your significant other to find—encourage him to write back.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Agree to disagree.
This is one of the most important relationship tips, as you both have strong opinions and therefore some issues will never be resolved. Respect each other’s point of view and agree not to argue about the same issue, unless it’s something that could get in the way of your future, like politics, religion, or values.<div id="amzn-assoc-ad-362ca55c-c25e-4b62-99e7-044b18860126"></div><script async src="//z-na.amazon-adsystem.com/widgets/onejs?MarketPlace=US&adInstanceId=362ca55c-c25e-4b62-99e7-044b18860126"></script></p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Set goals.
In addition to setting life goals, set relationship goals. For example: We aim to spend more time together outside rather than in front of the TV.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Take responsibility for your own happiness
Love is grand, but at the end of the day the only person we can hold accountable for our happiness is ourselves. Do volunteer work, exercise, host dinner parties—find what satisfies you, and go from there.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Learn each other’s conflict habits.
Make an effort to understand you and your partner’s conflict habits so you can break bad patterns and find a middle ground that’s productive and respectful.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Define love.
While “I love you,” is an extraordinary thing to say—and an equally wonderful thing to hear—it means something different to each person. Tell each other what you’re saying when you declare these magic words. It could be a list of many sentiments such as, “I would do anything for you,” and “I trust you completely.”</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Take turns planning date nights that are actual, real, capital-D Dates
Takeout and TV doesn’t count.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Approach your partner’s issues in the context of how they affect the relationship.
It’ll reduce the chances they feel personally attacked for no reason.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Cuddle.
Make ample time for cuddling. Whether or not it leads to sex, physical affection is important.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Don’t forget to say “I Like You.”
The greatest compliment you can give a partner (especially a long-term partner) is reminding them that not only do you love them, but also like them.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Have a spontaneous midday tryst.
Send him a text as he’s about to go on his lunch break, take time out on a Saturday, however you want to play it.
Photo: Imaxtree
Photo: Imaxtree</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Travel together.
Seeing the world together creates amazing shared memories.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Tell them EXACTLY why you love and appreciate them as often as possible.
“I love you” is good. “I love the way you make sure no one ever feels left out” is even better.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Stay out of their family drama.
It’s so not worth it.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Really look at each other.
We spend a lot of time with our partners but sometimes we don’t actually see them. Take the time to actually look into one another’s eyes.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Give each other a pet name.
It may be super annoying to other people (and you may want to reserve it for when you’re in private), but a pet name can add an extra layer of intimacy to your relationship.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Spend time alone.
As important as it is to spend quality time with your partner, it’s equally necessary that you develop a good sense of who you are without them. Kahlil Gibran said “let there be spaces in your togetherness,” and we stand by that.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Eat at the dinner table.
Do you eat in front of the TV? Try actually sitting down to a meal with your partner at an actual table. You may find it a welcome change.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>In fact, turn the TV off all together.
Why not try instituting a TV-free night in your apartment? See what else happens when you spend time together sans the talking box.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Ask for clarity.
If you’re confused about what your partner means, ask for clarity instead of making assumptions about what they mean. Use an open phrase like, “What did you mean when you said, ‘xyz'” rather than instantly going on the offensive.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Own your feelings.
Passive-aggressiveness is a total relationship killer. Quash it by practicing assertiveness and clarity. Saying “I’m fine” when you’re not fine is a prime example of not owning your feelings.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Communicate in a constructive way.
For instance, we think the phrase construction “When <em><em>_ happens, it makes me feel </em>_</em>” can be particularly helpful.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Take an interest in what your partner’s into.
He’s into chess, or cheese, or cheese that looks like a chess board (maybe?). You don’t have to love it, but give it a shot. You may surprise yourself!</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>But also cultivate your own.
You and your partner don’t need to have everything in common. Seriously. That’s actually really annoying.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Let your partner teach you something they’re good at, and vice versa.
Everyone—everyone—loves the feeling of being able to teach somebody they like about something they’re good at.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Bring your groups together.
It’s easy to silo your social lives and create separate his-and-hers worlds, but bringing your friends, siblings, or colleagues together can be a fun thing.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Don’t forget about sex.
Work, stress, and other responsibilities can get in the way of your sex life, and before you know it, you’ve gone a month without getting busy. Don’t let this happen. Schedule it in if you have to, just make sure to connect in an intimate way.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>But do forget about jealousy.
Jealousy can be completely toxic to relationships, so keep yours in check. If you’re always jealous, figure out if it’s your personal issue, or if your partner is doing things to appear less trustworthy.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Cultivate your appreciation.
Spread what you love about your partner. Practice your appreciation by sharing it with others— not in a gross, gratuitous, braggy way, but don’t miss out on the opportunity to tell others why your partner is awesome. In turn, it’ll remind you why you like them, too.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Laugh. In bed.
Sex should be sexy, sure. But it should also be fun. Don’t be afraid to have a laugh if things take a turn for the ridiculous.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Let yourself be taken care of when you need it.We all need special care on occasion. Let your partner help you when you’re feeling sick or down. It doesn’t mean you’re not strong, it just means you’re willing to accept help.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Check your competitive edge.
You and your partner are there to support each other, not compete with one another. If you find yourself comparing yourself or competing with your significant other, check your behavior. That’s not healthy!</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Have a bed day.
Allow yourselves a totally lazy day where you lie around and do nothing of note except enjoy each other’s company.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Be kind to yourself.
The best way to develop positive patterns in a relationship is to develop them first with yourself. Don’t be so critical of yourself, and you’ll set a good example for your relationship.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Express gratitude for the little things, and for specific things.
Big gestures are great, but it’s great to recognize the little things your partner does that make you feel happy and loved, too.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Date like you dated in high school.
Ask each other out. Get excited. Take forever to get ready. Make out. Repeat.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Be present.
We can ruin a perfectly great relationship by focusing too much on the past, or worrying too much about what may happen in the future. Learn to enjoy where you are, and who you’re with right now.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Don’t try to control.
A relationship isn’t a battle of wills, it’s two people who are choosing to be together, so don’t treat your partner like they’re some kind of wild animal you’re trying to tame.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Embrace your common goals.
What is it that you both want to accomplish? Can you support each other to reach those goals? That’ll be a big piece of what will hold you two to together as a couple in the long run.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Have a cultural experience together.
See a movie, a play, or an art exhibition together — and then talk about them afterward. You may be pleasantly surprised by how differently—or similarly—you viewed things.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Go on a long bike ride.
Bike rides are deeply freeing experiences, and it’s nice to be able to do that with someone you love.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Try talking on the phone. Yes, we know this sounds crazy, but phone calls are a different sort of communication than texting, or even in person communicating will allow. You may actually deepen your connection through a phone chat.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Make a mix for each other. It’s cute, romantic and something out of a rom-com. Although in this day and age, you might want to make a Spotify playlist rather than a mixed CD.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Keep yourself in check. We spend so much time paying attention to how our partners behave, but take a second to notice how you’re acting — especially if you’re fired up or in a bad mood. And then give yourself a second to…</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Breathe. Before you say something you don’t mean, take a breath and ask yourself if that’s really the way you want to move forward. Chances are, taking a second out will help you recalibrate and think of a more constructive way of handling the situation.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Help each other. This one is so easy, but if your partner’s having a hard time with something — whether it’s doing their taxes or organizing their closet — offer a helping hand.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Be their biggest cheerleader. If your partner’s accomplished something amazing, let them know it, and let them shine.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>In your craziest moments of frustration or anger, remember what it is that you like about them the most. There’s a reason you’re with them after all, right?</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Remember that a relationship should always make your life better on the whole, not worse. And aim to make sure yours is doing just that. If it’s not, it may be time to reconsider.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Enjoy the quiet moments you spend with each other. Not everything has to be a big adventure or a big deal Sometimes the best times are the quiet unplanned things you do together.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Make sure you’re taking care of yourself. Don’t let yourself get so invested in your partner that you forget to take care of yourself.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Let go of the past. We often let our past hurts dictate our present. Learn to let go of past resentments and fears in order to live more fully with your partner right now.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Touch each other often. Simple touch builds intimacy — espeically non-sexual touch. It’s a non-verbal way of saying, “yes, I’m here for you, and I care about you” and it helps reinforce your emotional bond.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>The best relationships are ones in which both partners feel like the luckiest person in the world. Find ways to communicate that and foster that feeling in each other, and you’ll be good.</p>
</li>
</ol>
</div>]]></description><link>https://live-smart.github.io/2017/07/21/102-Tips-To-Improve-Your-Relationship.html</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://live-smart.github.io/2017/07/21/102-Tips-To-Improve-Your-Relationship.html</guid><category><![CDATA[tips]]></category><category><![CDATA[relationship]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[Smart Buddy]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2017 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Let's Help Stray Cats]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div id="preamble">
<div class="sectionbody">
<div class="paragraph">
<p><strong>Sharing is caring. Please share this article with more people so that they do right things while helping stray cats.</strong></p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Feral cats, wild cats, stray cats&#8201;&#8212;&#8201;we have many names for the mysterious felines we sometimes see peeking out from under our porch or darting into abandoned buildings. Yet most of them share a single destiny: short, difficult lives.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Fortunately, helping feral or abandoned cats isn’t difficult. We have some tips on how to make a difference in the lives of our feline friends who are living on the edge.</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect3">
<h4 id="_how_the_problem_of_feral_cats_multiplies">How the Problem of Feral Cats Multiplies</h4>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>First, what is a feral cat? A feral cat is any cat who is too poorly socialized to be handled &#8230;&#8203; and who cannot be placed into a typical pet home.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p><strong><a href="http://amzn.to/2B8qR8I">Soft Padded Fleece Pet Bed by 2PET</a> (donates a portion of sales to various pet shelters &amp; charities)</strong></p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>According to the People for the Ethical Treatment of Animals, there are between 60 million and 100 million feral cats in the U.S. They are usually the offspring of cats who were lost or abandoned by their owners, and they grow up not socialized to humans.</p>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect3">
<h4 id="_how_are_they_linked">How are they linked?</h4>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Because a female cat can become pregnant as young as 16 weeks of age and go on to have two or three litters a year, the feral cat population&#8201;&#8212;&#8201;and the problems associated with it&#8201;&#8212;&#8201;grows and perpetuates. In seven years, a single female cat and her kittens can produce 420,000 more cats.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Feral cats often live in vacant lots, dodge cars, and eat from trash cans; face infection, disease, and an endless cycle of pregnancy; and suffer extremes in treatment and weather. The life of a feral, stray, or abandoned cat is often short, sometimes lasting for just two or three years.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Of course, feral cats also leave issues on the human doorstep&#8201;&#8212;&#8201;including noisy fights, odor, urinating to mark territory (also known as "spraying" or "marking"), flea infestations, and the inevitable breeding that creates even more unwanted cats.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Many experts agree that one of the best ways to help feral cats and cat groups&#8201;&#8212;&#8201;called colonies&#8201;&#8212;&#8201;is through neutering programs.</p>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect3">
<h4 id="_trap_neuter_return_programs_the_key_to_helping_cats">Trap-Neuter-Return Programs: The Key to Helping Cats</h4>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Trap-neuter-return (TNR) endeavors are geared toward reducing the number of unwanted cats by catching and then neutering or spaying them. Also called trap-neuter-spay-return or trap-neuter-vaccinate-return, they are endorsed by both the ASPCA and Humane Society.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>According to web site of the American Association of Feline Practitioners, stray and feral cats are “humanely trapped, examined, vaccinated, and surgically sterilized by veterinarians.” Feral cats are then returned to their familiar environment and, hopefully, cared for by volunteers, who may provide food and shelter, and monitor them for sickness.</p>
</div>
<div id="amzn-assoc-ad-0c0dd2ae-7302-48fb-b1b1-53bca831adb9"></div><script async src="//z-na.amazon-adsystem.com/widgets/onejs?MarketPlace=US&adInstanceId=0c0dd2ae-7302-48fb-b1b1-53bca831adb9"></script>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Proponents say the advantages include:</p>
</div>
<div class="ulist">
<ul>
<li>
<p>Neutered cats tend to gain weight and have fewer health problems&#8201;&#8212;&#8201;such as breast, testicular, and uterine cancer. Spaying also reduces the risks that go along with pregnancy. Fewer females in heat also means fewer toms attracted to an area, and so fewer risky cat fights.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Spaying and neutering feral cats offers population control. Behaviors like fighting and marking are also reduced, while benefits such as rodent control continue. Ultimately, less cat suffering also means less human suffering in the face of dying or injured cats.</p>
</li>
</ul>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Not everyone is a fan of TNR. Some fish and wildlife advocates maintain that re-releasing feral cats after neutering simply constitutes re-abandonment and doesn’t permanently address the larger problem.</p>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect3">
<h4 id="_the_problem_with_relocation_and_eradication">The Problem With Relocation and Eradication</h4>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Some people advocate relocating or “putting down” feral cats instead. Relocation may sound like a humane solution, but it is ultimately ineffective due to the “vacuum effect.” Feral cats gather where there are resources: food, water, and shelter. When an existing colony is relocated (or eradicated), before long a new flock of feral cats will discover the same resources and move in to “fill the vacuum.”</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Relocation is unappealing for other reasons. Because cats are very territorial, a relocated cat may try to find its way home, suffering accident or death on the way. The relocation area may already have an established colony or it may lack food, water, or shelter. Unless a colony’s life is in danger, most experts agree that relocation is almost always a bad solution.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Most people are not willing to support eradication, either. With a TNR effort, “people will give their time, money, and resources,” says Slater, author of <a href="http://amzn.to/2yROHPT" target="_blank">Community Approaches to Feral Cats</a>. “But if you’re catching and euthanizing cats, in most cases you just won’t get volunteers to do that.”</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>She also sees TNR as a teaching tool. “It gets people to think about how we can prevent cats from ending up on the street and how we can manage cat populations.”</p>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect3">
<h4 id="_why_feral_cat_adoption_is_not_an_option">Why Feral Cat Adoption Is Not an Option</h4>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Many experts agree that feral adult cats simply can’t be tamed. They are wild animals, like raccoons. They tend to stay away from humans, hide during the day, and when adopted, are very difficult to socialize. Just like you would never try to handle a raccoon, you should never try to pick up a feral cat. Call for assistance from the humane society or other animal welfare center.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>The ASPCA advocates adopting the many available domestic cats and kittens rather than trying to tame feral cats.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>However, feral kittens&#8201;&#8212;&#8201;especially those less than 8 weeks old&#8201;&#8212;&#8201;often can be socialized. Abandoned and lost cats can also be reintroduced to domestic living.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>How can you tell a stray from a feral cat? Lost or abandoned felines are usually comfortable around people and will frequently attempt to live near humans&#8201;&#8212;&#8201;under porches, or in garages, sheds, or backyards.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Still, Slater maintains that TNR is the most humane and effective long-term solution. “What we’ve done historically hasn’t gotten us anywhere,” she says. “We need to try something different. We’re not talking about neutering cats and then dumping them. What we’re really talking about is managed colonies, with a human feeding the cats, caring for them, getting them health care, providing them shelter.”</p>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect3">
<h4 id="_5_ways_you_can_help_stray_and_feral_cats">5 Ways You Can Help Stray and Feral Cats</h4>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>From little to big, there are many ways to help stray and feral cats. Here are some, beginning with one you can do at home:</p>
</div>
<div class="ulist">
<ul>
<li>
<p>Don’t contribute to the problem. “It goes without saying that you should spay and neuter your own cats,” says Linda P. Case, MS, author of Canine and Feline Behavior and Training: A Complete Guide to Understanding Our Two Best Friends. She also suggests keeping your cat indoors&#8201;&#8212;&#8201;not only for her safety, but also to prevent her from getting lost and ending up part of a feral colony.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Don’t feed and forget feral cats. Feeding feral and stray cats is generous, but they need health care as well. If you can’t manage ongoing care, “at the very least, get the cat neutered,” suggests Case.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Show your care with cash. A little money can go a long way to help a cat. Spay/neuter surgeries may cost as little as $17 for shelters to perform, so a single $20 donation can dramatically change the life of a feral cat. Contact your nearest Humane Society to find out if they’ve got a TNR program; if they don’t, they’ll know who does. You can also donate money to animal welfare groups through an estate or will.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Volunteer your time. TNR and similar programs are often run by nonprofit organizations that rely on volunteer help. If you can’t aid in a clinical setting, you can be involved at the community level&#8201;&#8212;&#8201;contacting local veterinarians and businesses, writing letters, fund-raising, or staffing a booth at a community event.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Become a colony caretaker. “In a managed colony, cats can live to be 12 to 16 years old,” says Slater. In fact, she adds, studies of 100,000 managed feral cats in TNR programs found that most were in good health. If you think you can provide ongoing shelter, food, or health care to a group of feral cats, contact your local Humane Society, veterinary hospital, or other animal welfare group to find out how to get started. But before you do, understand that committing to care for a colony is a big responsibility. The colony will become dependent on you, just as a domestic cat would be. If you go away or move, it’s vital you find someone else to care for the cats in your absence.</p>
</li>
</ul>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>“As part of living in a civilized society, it is our obligation to look after those who are weak, sick, or powerless,” says Slater. “Our responsibility includes our domestic animals, whom we took from the wild and made dependent on us.”</p>
</div>
</div>]]></description><link>https://live-smart.github.io/2017/04/11/Lets-Help-Stray-Cats.html</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://live-smart.github.io/2017/04/11/Lets-Help-Stray-Cats.html</guid><category><![CDATA[stray cats]]></category><category><![CDATA[cats]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[Smart Buddy]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2017 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Allergy, Dust Mites, and Solution]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="paragraph">
<p>Have you ever experienced symptoms of allergy such as rhinitis, nasal congestion, asthma, urticaria? I&#8217;ve had serious rhinitis and nasal congestion during sleep since I was born, and absolutely no idea what has gone wrong. I tried different treatments such as ephedrine nasal spray, septum reconstructomy, polypectomy, none of which really worked. I&#8217;ve been waking up during mid of night just to get some air before I suffocate. That is until recently after I found a solution for this, one that solves it for good.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>During my research, I found that my symptoms might be related to allergy to something, but I had no idea what that was. Some further digging pointed me to dust mites.</p>
</div>
<div class="quoteblock">
<blockquote>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>The house dust mite (HDM) is a major perennial allergen source and a significant cause of allergic rhinitis and allergic asthma.</p>
</div>
</blockquote>
<div class="attribution">
&#8212; Respiratory allergy caused by house dust mites: What do we really know?
</div>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p><a href="http://www.jacionline.org/article/S0091-6749(14)01482-1/abstract?cc=y=">Link to it</a></p>
</div>
<div class="quoteblock">
<blockquote>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Dust mites may be the most common trigger of year-round allergies and asthma.</p>
</div>
</blockquote>
<div class="attribution">
&#8212; Dust Mite Allergy
</div>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p><a href="http://www.aafa.org/page/dust-mite-allergy.aspx">Link to it</a></p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Since I don&#8217;t have sofa and carpets, a major point where dust mites can thrive should be inferrably my bed or more specifically the mattress. How can I get those tiny bugs out of my mattress? I did quite a few research on this. There are youtube videos introducing heating methods for killing dust mites, which are more or less one off and won&#8217;t solve the problem over time. What I need is something repeatable and that can solve the perennial problem the sustainable way.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>That leads me to vacuum based solutions. I found <a href="https://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B01910SH8G/ref=as_li_qf_sp_asin_il_tl?ie=UTF8&amp;tag=livesmart08-20&amp;camp=1789&amp;creative=9325&amp;linkCode=as2&amp;creativeASIN=B01910SH8G&amp;linkId=2352c1144a335df35af1b62d36ea86d3">Rainbow</a></p>
</div>
<div class="imageblock">
<div class="content">
<a class="image" href="https://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B01910SH8G/ref=as_li_tl?ie=UTF8&camp=1789&creative=9325&creativeASIN=B01910SH8G&linkCode=as2&tag=livesmart08-20&linkId=de60bbbcc8e3cabf92f504791468f3a0"><img src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/19504323/33869807-d2dfbb1a-df45-11e7-9c59-b7122a26bfec.png" alt="33869807 d2dfbb1a df45 11e7 9c59 b7122a26bfec.png"></a>
</div>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>But this looks more like overkill and really requires some good space to store it. A better option is <a href="https://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B00SMLJPKA/ref=as_li_qf_sp_asin_il_tl?ie=UTF8&amp;tag=livesmart08-20&amp;camp=1789&amp;creative=9325&amp;linkCode=as2&amp;creativeASIN=B00SMLJPKA&amp;linkId=e022a1567aed7d0cfa75b89fcb880ae7">Dyson V6</a>. It&#8217;s completely cordless and battery-based. A full charge as I tested can last around 20 minutes of working at its full capacity (strong mode). The suction power is really outstanding. With the <a href="https://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B0017R6ZO0/ref=as_li_qf_sp_asin_il_tl?ie=UTF8&amp;tag=livesmart08-20&amp;camp=1789&amp;creative=9325&amp;linkCode=as2&amp;creativeASIN=B0017R6ZO0&amp;linkId=955f051110948cca65849f26d9c09ea3">mini turbine head</a> (see below) which comes with V6 Absolute model, I&#8217;m basically able to suck all dust mites, their remains, my own dead skin and dandruff out of my mattress.</p>
</div>
<div class="imageblock">
<div class="content">
<a class="image" href="https://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B00062MT7E/ref=as_li_tl?ie=UTF8&camp=1789&creative=9325&creativeASIN=B00062MT7E&linkCode=as2&tag=livesmart08-20&linkId=9aac2ee60d48806f4ba60b358837bc8b"><img src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/19504323/33869902-495d8664-df46-11e7-9582-3460be6fbc32.png" alt="33869902 495d8664 df46 11e7 9582 3460be6fbc32.png"></a>
</div>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>It surprises me that a clean normal looking mattress can contain such amount of powder like stuff:</p>
</div>
<div class="imageblock">
<div class="content">
<a class="image" href="https://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B00SMLJPKA/ref=as_li_qf_sp_asin_il_tl?ie=UTF8&tag=livesmart08-20&camp=1789&creative=9325&linkCode=as2&creativeASIN=B00SMLJPKA&linkId=e022a1567aed7d0cfa75b89fcb880ae7"><img src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/19504323/16232379/dc0349ce-37fc-11e6-9514-2fd02a2a3f0e.jpg" alt="dc0349ce 37fc 11e6 9514 2fd02a2a3f0e.jpg"></a>
</div>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>And much better sleep for me ever after the first campaign of removing dust mites!</p>
</div>]]></description><link>https://live-smart.github.io/2016/06/17/Allergy-Dust-Mites-and-Solution.html</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://live-smart.github.io/2016/06/17/Allergy-Dust-Mites-and-Solution.html</guid><category><![CDATA[allergy]]></category><category><![CDATA[dust mite]]></category><category><![CDATA[bed]]></category><category><![CDATA[mattress]]></category><category><![CDATA[vacuum]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[Smart Buddy]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2016 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Shoes and Knee Pain]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="sect3">
<h4 id="_update_on_dec_13_2017">Update on Dec 13, 2017</h4>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Hoka One One has released more and better models since this post was originally written. Here are some great ones that have improved in every aspect:</p>
</div>
<div class="ulist">
<ul>
<li>
<p><a href="http://amzn.to/2AAH0U4">Clifton 4 (Men)</a></p>
</li>
<li>
<p><a href="http://amzn.to/2BZF1ok">Clifton 4 (Women)</a></p>
</li>
<li>
<p><a href="http://amzn.to/2Bi3fxG">Bondi 5 (Men)</a></p>
</li>
<li>
<p><a href="http://amzn.to/2nUQROp">Bondi 5 (Women)</a></p>
</li>
</ul>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect2">
<h3 id="_original_post">Original Post</h3>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Knee pain is commonly witnessed among people of all ages. Causes can vary but the most significant yet often overlooked one is shoes. How would you pick a pair of shoes that would ease or prevent knee damage / knee pain?</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>There are 3 major factors that contribute to the comfort level of shoes.</p>
</div>
<div class="olist arabic">
<ol class="arabic">
<li>
<p>Arch support</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Ankle support</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Heel Cushioning</p>
</li>
</ol>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>&#8203;<br></p>
</div>
<div class="sect3">
<h4 id="_arch_support">Arch Support</h4>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>The arch is perhaps the most important structural feature of our feet, which bear 200,000 to 300,000 lbs. of weight each mile we walk. Arches absorb the brunt of the pressure our bodies thrust upon our feet with each stride. Properly supporting the arch can prevent a variety of musculoskeletal problems that can lead to inactivity and even disability.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p><span class="image"><img src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/19504323/15632485/b4cd98a8-25c5-11e6-8c46-2b222e525c75.jpg" alt="b4cd98a8 25c5 11e6 8c46 2b222e525c75.jpg"></span></p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>&#8203;<br></p>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect3">
<h4 id="_ankle_support">Ankle Support</h4>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>It really depends on what kind of ankle you have. If yours is iffy, it would generally be safer to pick a pair of shoes that provides great ankle support.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Here&#8217;s a lacing technique that would help as well:</p>
</div>
<iframe width="640" height="360" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/Cq-Ar0zzFTI?rel=0" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>&#8203;<br></p>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect3">
<h4 id="_heel_cushioning">Heel Cushioning</h4>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>The risk of knee injury is increased by physical changes as joint cartilage that absorbs shock, becomes thinner with aging, weight gain and muscle loss. Great running shoes are designed to cushion your feet, which in turn takes stress off your knees.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p><span class="image"><img src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/19504323/15452729/4993684a-202c-11e6-9efb-232c71ebd5c8.jpg" alt="4993684a 202c 11e6 9efb 232c71ebd5c8.jpg"></span></p>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect3">
<h4 id="_recommendations">Recommendations</h4>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>When it comes to running safe and in comfort, maximalist shoes are definitely the number one option to go for. And guess who&#8217;s the king of maximalists?</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Introducing Hoka One One. It is a French manufacturing company that designs and markets generously soled and extremely light weight running shoes for distance runners. Noted for their light weight and maximal cushioning, Hoka running shoes are dubbed as "maximalist shoes", in contrast to minimalist shoes. In 2010, it introduced the original <a href="http://amzn.to/1TTW0zT">Mafate</a>, a running shoe boasting two to three times the amount of cushioning as other running shoes on the market.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>So which model would you fit into? Here I picked a list of Hokas that are best for knee protection:</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p><strong>Vanquish 2</strong></p>
</div>
<div class="imageblock">
	<div class="content">

<a class="image" href="http://www.amazon.com/Hoka-One-Vanquish-Black-Running/dp/B00ZUYP0CY/ref=as_li_ss_il?ie=UTF8&qid=1465035208&sr=8-1&keywords=hoka+one+one+vanquish+2&linkCode=li2&tag=livesmart08-20&linkId=364785b81d6e9356b85cab7a91eae30d" target="_blank"><img border="0" src="//ws-na.amazon-adsystem.com/widgets/q?_encoding=UTF8&ASIN=B00ZUYP0CY&Format=_SL500_&ID=AsinImage&MarketPlace=US&ServiceVersion=20070822&WS=1&tag=livesmart08-20" ></a><img src="//ir-na.amazon-adsystem.com/e/ir?t=livesmart08-20&l=li2&o=1&a=B00ZUYP0CY" width="1" height="1" border="0" alt="" style="border:none !important; margin:0px !important;" />

    </div>
	<div class="title">

Hoka completely overhauled this cushy neutral shoe for 2016, making it lighter and more energetic. Weights: 9.8 oz. (men’s 9.0); 8.3 oz. (women’s 7.0). Heel-Toe Offset: 5mm; 32mm (heel), 27mm (forefoot)

    </div>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>&#8203;<br></p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p><strong>Bondi 4</strong></p>
</div>
<div class="imageblock">
	<div class="content">

<a href="http://www.amazon.com/Hoka-One-Bondi-Directoire-Running/dp/B01071HR84/ref=as_li_ss_il?ie=UTF8&qid=1465039586&sr=8-1&keywords=hoka+one+one+bondi+4&linkCode=li3&tag=livesmart08-20&linkId=9d6d5b6a3abdd83073e5acb0716c1567" target="_blank"><img border="0" src="//ws-na.amazon-adsystem.com/widgets/q?_encoding=UTF8&ASIN=B01071HR84&Format=_SL500_&ID=AsinImage&MarketPlace=US&ServiceVersion=20070822&WS=1&tag=livesmart08-20" ></a><img src="//ir-na.amazon-adsystem.com/e/ir?t=livesmart08-20&l=li3&o=1&a=B01071HR84" width="1" height="1" border="0" alt="" style="border:none !important; margin:0px !important;" />

    </div>
	<div class="title">

With one of the thickest midsoles in the marketplace, the Bondi is in an extreme class of high-off-the-ground, oversized cushioning shoes. But it’s not just the amount of cushioning, it’s the balance of the shoe and its unique design features—specifically the rockered profile, beveled heel and significant toe spring—that make running in the Bondi 4 such an exalted experience. weights: 10.6 oz. (men’s), 9.4 oz. (women’s); heel-toe offset: 4mm; 37mm (heel), 33mm (forefoot) for men; 34mm (heel), 30mm (forefoot) for women

    </div>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>&#8203;<br></p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p><strong>Clifton 2</strong></p>
</div>
<div class="imageblock">
	<div class="content">

<a href="http://www.amazon.com/Hoka-One-Clifton-Directoire-Running/dp/B011PM8K12/ref=as_li_ss_il?ie=UTF8&qid=1465039691&sr=8-1&keywords=hoka+one+one+clifton+3&linkCode=li2&tag=livesmart08-20&linkId=2bd56d3fe715fa108766ec3f0553388f" target="_blank"><img border="0" src="//ws-na.amazon-adsystem.com/widgets/q?_encoding=UTF8&ASIN=B011PM8K12&Format=_SL500_&ID=AsinImage&MarketPlace=US&ServiceVersion=20070822&WS=1&tag=livesmart08-20" ></a><img src="//ir-na.amazon-adsystem.com/e/ir?t=livesmart08-20&l=li2&o=1&a=B011PM8K12" width="1" height="1" border="0" alt="" style="border:none !important; margin:0px !important;" />

    </div>
	<div class="title">

Hoka made a few small but significant tweaks to the award-winning Clifton for 2016, most notably making it a few millimeters wider in the forefoot and replacing the overlays on the upper with a sleeker, seamless TPU-reinforced mesh. ($130, 5mm heel-toe offset, 8.6 oz.)

    </div>
</div>
</div>
</div>]]></description><link>https://live-smart.github.io/2016/03/05/Shoes-and-Knee-Pain.html</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://live-smart.github.io/2016/03/05/Shoes-and-Knee-Pain.html</guid><category><![CDATA[knee]]></category><category><![CDATA[knee pain]]></category><category><![CDATA[knee protection]]></category><category><![CDATA[shoe]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[Smart Buddy]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sat, 05 Mar 2016 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>