<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Live Smart]]></title><description><![CDATA[Quality Life, Money Saving, Smart Shopping]]></description><link>https://live-smart.github.io</link><image><url>https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/19504323/15453331/828a4ae8-2044-11e6-83e3-e1153288e4d9.jpeg</url><title>Live Smart</title><link>https://live-smart.github.io</link></image><generator>RSS for Node</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2017 14:55:43 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://live-smart.github.io/rss/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><ttl>60</ttl><item><title><![CDATA[Some Great Books on Investment]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div id="preamble">
<div class="sectionbody">
<div class="paragraph">
<p>It&#8217;s imperative for young adults and professionals to start investing early. One of the main reasons for doing so is to obtain the power of compound interest; by holding long-term investments, one can allow his or her assets to generate more returns. Investing just a few years earlier could translate into tens of thousands, if not hundreds of thousands, of additional funds for your retirement nest egg.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>But while it is important to invest early, it is also important to invest wisely. These five classic investing books can provide indispensable business and finance insights for young investors.</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect2">
<h3 id="__a_href_http_amzn_to_2av1vrp_rich_dad_poor_dad_2000_a_by_robert_kiyosaki"><a href="http://amzn.to/2Av1Vrp">"Rich Dad, Poor Dad" (2000)</a> by Robert Kiyosaki</h3>
<div class="imageblock">
<div class="content">
<a class="image" href="http://amzn.to/2Av1Vrp"><img src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/19504323/33874370-7a2599a4-df59-11e7-86f1-453de69da698.png" alt="33874370 7a2599a4 df59 11e7 86f1 453de69da698.png"></a>
</div>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>This classic is a must-read for young investors. Kiyosaki&#8217;s view is that the poor and middle class work for money, but the rich work to learn. He stresses the importance of financial literacy, and presents financial independence as the ultimate goal, and a way to avoid the rat race of corporate America. The author points out that while accounting is important to learn, it can also be misleading. Banks label a house as an asset for the individual, but because of the required payments to keep it, it can really be a liability in terms of cash flow. Real assets add cash flow to your wallet.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Kiyosaki advocates investments that produce periodic cash flow for the investor while providing upside in terms of equity value. Real estate investments and stocks that provide dividends are viewed favorably. The author advises that America&#8217;s educational system is designed to keep people working hard for the rest of their lives, and that the school system does a poor job of teaching people to create enough wealth so they won&#8217;t have to work anymore. Kiyosaki also highlights the importance of tax planning.</p>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect2">
<h3 id="__a_href_http_amzn_to_2ayfwba_the_essays_of_warren_buffett_lessons_for_corporate_america_1997_a_by_warren_buffett"><a href="http://amzn.to/2AYFWbA">"The Essays of Warren Buffett: Lessons For Corporate America" (1997)</a> by Warren Buffett</h3>
<div class="imageblock">
<div class="content">
<a class="image" href="http://amzn.to/2AYFWbA"><img src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/19504323/33874451-d45575ca-df59-11e7-82a2-278ecb536ae8.png" alt="33874451 d45575ca df59 11e7 82a2 278ecb536ae8.png"></a>
</div>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>In his essays, Warren Buffett—widely considered to be modern history&#8217;s most successful investor—provides his views on a variety of topics important to corporate America and shareholders. Young investors can get a glimpse of the interface between a company&#8217;s management and its shareholders, as well as the thought processes involved in enhancing a company&#8217;s enterprise value.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Buffett&#8217;s essays include discussions on corporate governance, finance, investing, alternatives to common stock, mergers and acquisitions, accounting and valuation, accounting policy, and tax matters. Buffett outlines his basic business principles, and as the steward of Berkshire Hathaway Inc. (BRK-A
), informs the shareholders of the company that their mutual interests are aligned. He has a philosophy of bringing in talented managers at portfolio companies and leaving them alone. He advocates purchasing shares of businesses at times when these stocks are trading at a discount from their inherent value. He opposes following investing trends.</p>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect2">
<h3 id="__a_href_http_amzn_to_2au8y3c_beating_the_street_1994_a_by_peter_lynch"><a href="http://amzn.to/2Au8Y3C">"Beating the Street" (1994)</a> by Peter Lynch</h3>
<div class="imageblock">
<div class="content">
<a class="image" href="http://amzn.to/2Au8Y3C"><img src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/19504323/33874512-044dd2d6-df5a-11e7-9a03-8ee3740e57ec.png" alt="33874512 044dd2d6 df5a 11e7 9a03 8ee3740e57ec.png"></a>
</div>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Peter Lynch is one of the most successful stock market investors and hedge fund managers of the 20th century. He started out as an intern at Fidelity Investments in the mid 1960s. Nearly 11 years later, he was tasked to manage the Magellan Fund, which at the time had close to $18 million in assets. By 1990, the fund had grown to a whopping $18 billion in assets with nearly 1,000 stock positions. During this time, the fund boasted average returns of more than 29% per year.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>"Beating The Street" allows the reader to peek into Lynch&#8217;s mind and thought processes in terms of deciding whether to buy or sell a stock. Lynch believes that an individual investor could exploit market opportunities better than Wall Street, and encourages investors to invest in what they know.</p>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect2">
<h3 id="__a_href_http_amzn_to_2kwffqb_the_intelligent_investor_1949_a_by_benjamin_graham"><a href="http://amzn.to/2kWFFQb">"The Intelligent Investor" (1949)</a> by Benjamin Graham</h3>
<div class="imageblock">
<div class="content">
<a class="image" href="http://amzn.to/2kWFFQb"><img src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/19504323/33874540-23efa4a2-df5a-11e7-84c2-e08ebc4353fa.png" alt="33874540 23efa4a2 df5a 11e7 84c2 e08ebc4353fa.png"></a>
</div>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>This book was written in 1949 and has been hailed by Warren Buffett as the best investing book ever written. Benjamin Graham is considered the "father of value investing." This paradigm advocates the purchase of stocks that appear under-priced relative to their inherent value, which is determined through fundamental analysis.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Graham delves into the history of the stock market, and informs the reader on conducting fundamental analysis on a stock. He discusses various ways of managing your portfolio including both a positive and defensive approach. He then compares the stocks of several companies to illustrate his points.</p>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect2">
<h3 id="__a_href_http_amzn_to_2yzumm1_think_and_grow_rich_1937_a_by_napoleon_hill"><a href="http://amzn.to/2yZumM1">"Think and Grow Rich" (1937)</a> by Napoleon Hill</h3>
<div class="imageblock">
<div class="content">
<a class="image" href="http://amzn.to/2yZumM1"><img src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/19504323/33874699-9dee87a0-df5a-11e7-8b1c-d58cc3629e0b.png" alt="33874699 9dee87a0 df5a 11e7 8b1c d58cc3629e0b.png"></a>
</div>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>"Think and Grow Rich" was written during the Great Depression, and has since sold more than 30 million copies worldwide. Hill conducted extensive research based on his associations with wealthy individuals during his lifetime. At the suggestion of Andrew Carnegie, Hill published 13 principles for success and personal achievement from his observations and research. These include desire, faith, specialized knowledge, organized planning, persistence and the "sixth sense." Hill also believed in brainstorming with like-minded people, whose efforts can create synergistic energy.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>This book conveys valuable insights into the psychology of success and abundance, and should be considered a priority read given the current age&#8217;s emphasis on shock-value entertainment and negative news.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>The best investors did not emerge overnight, but honed their skills through years of thought, research and practice. When you are done with these books, here are several more to add to your reading list.</p>
</div>
</div>]]></description><link>https://live-smart.github.io/2018/11/28/Some-Great-Books-on-Investment.html</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://live-smart.github.io/2018/11/28/Some-Great-Books-on-Investment.html</guid><category><![CDATA[investment]]></category><category><![CDATA[make money]]></category><category><![CDATA[revenue]]></category><category><![CDATA[income]]></category><category><![CDATA[profit]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[Smart Buddy]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Diet for Programmers / Software Engineers / Hackers / Geeks]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="paragraph">
<p>Are you a software developer / engineer who, like virtually any other out there has a "beer belly" to deal with? Is your career surging while your health is spiraling down? Has your doctor told you to cut calories in your diet and do more exercises?</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Well, it&#8217;d probably be hard for you to squeeze 15 minutes out everyday to do exercises. Those drinking sessions are probably hard to avoid too. Is there a solid way to fix all these, flatten the belly and make the life a bit easier and healthier?</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p><a href="http://amzn.to/2AVVPPY">Balanced Greens Organic Vegan Protein Powder</a> to the rescue.</p>
</div>
<div class="imageblock">
<div class="content">
<a class="image" href="http://amzn.to/2AVVPPY"><img src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/19504323/33814649-99fd13e0-de66-11e7-814b-54b73d4a35af.png" alt="33814649 99fd13e0 de66 11e7 814b 54b73d4a35af.png"></a>
</div>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Being completely organic, it&#8217;s an all-in-one probiotics, antioxidants, fiber and digestive enzymes meal replacement shake which targets to alkalize, energize and detox your body. No bother with seeking and preparing ingredients yourself anymore. They&#8217;re all in there.</p>
</div>
<div class="imageblock">
<div class="content">
<a class="image" href="http://amzn.to/2AVVPPY"><img src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/19504323/33814651-9f56b2ce-de66-11e7-8816-ea0ac79ce7ab.png" alt="33814651 9f56b2ce de66 11e7 8816 ea0ac79ce7ab.png"></a>
</div>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p><strong>Fiber</strong> for example, is one of weight loss&#8217;s little secrets. The main structural component of plants, fiber can&#8217;t be digested by the human body. Its primary purpose is to add bulk to the contents of your stomach and digestive tract, which helps move things along and keeps you regular. As a bonus, the extra bulk in your belly helps fill you up and keep you feeling full so you can limit your calorie intake. Having a fiber-rich shake as a snack or meal replacement each day just might be what you need to shed those extra pounds. Fiber-rich foods, such as fruits, vegetables and whole grains, tend to be healthy and low in energy density, or calories per gram. Eating a lot of low-energy-dense foods helps fill you up on fewer calories so you can control your calorie intake to lose weight. According to a review published in "Nutrition" in March 2005, dietary fiber intake is inversely associated with body weight; people who eat more fiber tend to weigh less and have less body fat.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Replacing one meal a day with a <a href="http://amzn.to/2AVVPPY">nutritious, high-fiber shake</a> can help you create the calorie deficit required for weight loss. To lose 1 to 2 pounds per week, which is considered a safe and healthy rate of weight loss, you need to trim 500 to 1,000 calories from your daily diet. If you normally go out for lunch with coworkers and take in 800 calories or more, skipping the lunch outing and whipping up a fiber-rich shake in the kitchen at your office can save you 500 calories. That one change is enough to lose 4 pounds in a month.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Ready to buff up your overall energy and health? <a href="http://amzn.to/2AVVPPY">Try it</a> now:)</p>
</div>]]></description><link>https://live-smart.github.io/2017/11/30/Best-Diet-for-Programmers-Software-Engineers-Hackers-Geeks.html</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://live-smart.github.io/2017/11/30/Best-Diet-for-Programmers-Software-Engineers-Hackers-Geeks.html</guid><category><![CDATA[diet]]></category><category><![CDATA[programmers]]></category><category><![CDATA[software engineers]]></category><category><![CDATA[hackers]]></category><category><![CDATA[geeks]]></category><category><![CDATA[health]]></category><category><![CDATA[shake]]></category><category><![CDATA[fibre]]></category><category><![CDATA[fiber]]></category><category><![CDATA[yoghurt]]></category><category><![CDATA[weight loss]]></category><category><![CDATA[probiotics]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[Smart Buddy]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2017 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>