<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Live Smart]]></title><description><![CDATA[Quality Life, Money Saving, Smart Shopping]]></description><link>https://live-smart.github.io</link><image><url>https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/19504323/15453331/828a4ae8-2044-11e6-83e3-e1153288e4d9.jpeg</url><title>Live Smart</title><link>https://live-smart.github.io</link></image><generator>RSS for Node</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2017 04:29:35 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://live-smart.github.io/rss/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><ttl>60</ttl><item><title><![CDATA[Some Great Books on Investment]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div id="preamble">
<div class="sectionbody">
<div class="paragraph">
<p>It&#8217;s imperative for young adults and professionals to start investing early. One of the main reasons for doing so is to obtain the power of compound interest; by holding long-term investments, one can allow his or her assets to generate more returns. Investing just a few years earlier could translate into tens of thousands, if not hundreds of thousands, of additional funds for your retirement nest egg.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>But while it is important to invest early, it is also important to invest wisely. These five classic investing books can provide indispensable business and finance insights for young investors.</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect2">
<h3 id="__a_href_http_amzn_to_2av1vrp_rich_dad_poor_dad_2000_a_by_robert_kiyosaki"><a href="http://amzn.to/2Av1Vrp">"Rich Dad, Poor Dad" (2000)</a> by Robert Kiyosaki</h3>
<div class="imageblock">
<div class="content">
<a class="image" href="http://amzn.to/2Av1Vrp"><img src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/19504323/33874370-7a2599a4-df59-11e7-86f1-453de69da698.png" alt="33874370 7a2599a4 df59 11e7 86f1 453de69da698.png"></a>
</div>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>This classic is a must-read for young investors. Kiyosaki&#8217;s view is that the poor and middle class work for money, but the rich work to learn. He stresses the importance of financial literacy, and presents financial independence as the ultimate goal, and a way to avoid the rat race of corporate America. The author points out that while accounting is important to learn, it can also be misleading. Banks label a house as an asset for the individual, but because of the required payments to keep it, it can really be a liability in terms of cash flow. Real assets add cash flow to your wallet.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Kiyosaki advocates investments that produce periodic cash flow for the investor while providing upside in terms of equity value. Real estate investments and stocks that provide dividends are viewed favorably. The author advises that America&#8217;s educational system is designed to keep people working hard for the rest of their lives, and that the school system does a poor job of teaching people to create enough wealth so they won&#8217;t have to work anymore. Kiyosaki also highlights the importance of tax planning.</p>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect2">
<h3 id="__a_href_http_amzn_to_2ayfwba_the_essays_of_warren_buffett_lessons_for_corporate_america_1997_a_by_warren_buffett"><a href="http://amzn.to/2AYFWbA">"The Essays of Warren Buffett: Lessons For Corporate America" (1997)</a> by Warren Buffett</h3>
<div class="imageblock">
<div class="content">
<a class="image" href="http://amzn.to/2AYFWbA"><img src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/19504323/33874451-d45575ca-df59-11e7-82a2-278ecb536ae8.png" alt="33874451 d45575ca df59 11e7 82a2 278ecb536ae8.png"></a>
</div>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>In his essays, Warren Buffett—widely considered to be modern history&#8217;s most successful investor—provides his views on a variety of topics important to corporate America and shareholders. Young investors can get a glimpse of the interface between a company&#8217;s management and its shareholders, as well as the thought processes involved in enhancing a company&#8217;s enterprise value.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Buffett&#8217;s essays include discussions on corporate governance, finance, investing, alternatives to common stock, mergers and acquisitions, accounting and valuation, accounting policy, and tax matters. Buffett outlines his basic business principles, and as the steward of Berkshire Hathaway Inc. (BRK-A
), informs the shareholders of the company that their mutual interests are aligned. He has a philosophy of bringing in talented managers at portfolio companies and leaving them alone. He advocates purchasing shares of businesses at times when these stocks are trading at a discount from their inherent value. He opposes following investing trends.</p>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect2">
<h3 id="__a_href_http_amzn_to_2au8y3c_beating_the_street_1994_a_by_peter_lynch"><a href="http://amzn.to/2Au8Y3C">"Beating the Street" (1994)</a> by Peter Lynch</h3>
<div class="imageblock">
<div class="content">
<a class="image" href="http://amzn.to/2Au8Y3C"><img src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/19504323/33874512-044dd2d6-df5a-11e7-9a03-8ee3740e57ec.png" alt="33874512 044dd2d6 df5a 11e7 9a03 8ee3740e57ec.png"></a>
</div>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Peter Lynch is one of the most successful stock market investors and hedge fund managers of the 20th century. He started out as an intern at Fidelity Investments in the mid 1960s. Nearly 11 years later, he was tasked to manage the Magellan Fund, which at the time had close to $18 million in assets. By 1990, the fund had grown to a whopping $18 billion in assets with nearly 1,000 stock positions. During this time, the fund boasted average returns of more than 29% per year.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>"Beating The Street" allows the reader to peek into Lynch&#8217;s mind and thought processes in terms of deciding whether to buy or sell a stock. Lynch believes that an individual investor could exploit market opportunities better than Wall Street, and encourages investors to invest in what they know.</p>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect2">
<h3 id="__a_href_http_amzn_to_2kwffqb_the_intelligent_investor_1949_a_by_benjamin_graham"><a href="http://amzn.to/2kWFFQb">"The Intelligent Investor" (1949)</a> by Benjamin Graham</h3>
<div class="imageblock">
<div class="content">
<a class="image" href="http://amzn.to/2kWFFQb"><img src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/19504323/33874540-23efa4a2-df5a-11e7-84c2-e08ebc4353fa.png" alt="33874540 23efa4a2 df5a 11e7 84c2 e08ebc4353fa.png"></a>
</div>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>This book was written in 1949 and has been hailed by Warren Buffett as the best investing book ever written. Benjamin Graham is considered the "father of value investing." This paradigm advocates the purchase of stocks that appear under-priced relative to their inherent value, which is determined through fundamental analysis.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Graham delves into the history of the stock market, and informs the reader on conducting fundamental analysis on a stock. He discusses various ways of managing your portfolio including both a positive and defensive approach. He then compares the stocks of several companies to illustrate his points.</p>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect2">
<h3 id="__a_href_http_amzn_to_2yzumm1_think_and_grow_rich_1937_a_by_napoleon_hill"><a href="http://amzn.to/2yZumM1">"Think and Grow Rich" (1937)</a> by Napoleon Hill</h3>
<div class="imageblock">
<div class="content">
<a class="image" href="http://amzn.to/2yZumM1"><img src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/19504323/33874699-9dee87a0-df5a-11e7-8b1c-d58cc3629e0b.png" alt="33874699 9dee87a0 df5a 11e7 8b1c d58cc3629e0b.png"></a>
</div>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>"Think and Grow Rich" was written during the Great Depression, and has since sold more than 30 million copies worldwide. Hill conducted extensive research based on his associations with wealthy individuals during his lifetime. At the suggestion of Andrew Carnegie, Hill published 13 principles for success and personal achievement from his observations and research. These include desire, faith, specialized knowledge, organized planning, persistence and the "sixth sense." Hill also believed in brainstorming with like-minded people, whose efforts can create synergistic energy.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>This book conveys valuable insights into the psychology of success and abundance, and should be considered a priority read given the current age&#8217;s emphasis on shock-value entertainment and negative news.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>The best investors did not emerge overnight, but honed their skills through years of thought, research and practice. When you are done with these books, here are several more to add to your reading list.</p>
</div>
</div>]]></description><link>https://live-smart.github.io/2018/11/28/Some-Great-Books-on-Investment.html</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://live-smart.github.io/2018/11/28/Some-Great-Books-on-Investment.html</guid><category><![CDATA[investment]]></category><category><![CDATA[make money]]></category><category><![CDATA[revenue]]></category><category><![CDATA[income]]></category><category><![CDATA[profit]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[Smart Buddy]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Best Diet for Programmers / Software Engineers / Hackers / Geeks]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="paragraph">
<p>Are you a software developer / engineer who, like virtually any other out there has a "beer belly" to deal with? Is your career surging while your health is spiraling down? Has your doctor told you to cut calories in your diet and do more exercises?</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Well, it&#8217;d probably be hard for you to squeeze 15 minutes out everyday to do exercises. Those drinking sessions are probably hard to avoid too. Is there a solid way to fix all these, flatten the belly and make the life a bit easier and healthier?</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p><a href="http://amzn.to/2AVVPPY">Balanced Greens Organic Vegan Protein Powder</a> to the rescue.</p>
</div>
<div class="imageblock">
<div class="content">
<a class="image" href="http://amzn.to/2AVVPPY"><img src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/19504323/33814649-99fd13e0-de66-11e7-814b-54b73d4a35af.png" alt="33814649 99fd13e0 de66 11e7 814b 54b73d4a35af.png"></a>
</div>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Being completely organic, it&#8217;s an all-in-one probiotics, antioxidants, fiber and digestive enzymes meal replacement shake which targets to alkalize, energize and detox your body. No bother with seeking and preparing ingredients yourself anymore. They&#8217;re all in there.</p>
</div>
<div class="imageblock">
<div class="content">
<a class="image" href="http://amzn.to/2AVVPPY"><img src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/19504323/33814651-9f56b2ce-de66-11e7-8816-ea0ac79ce7ab.png" alt="33814651 9f56b2ce de66 11e7 8816 ea0ac79ce7ab.png"></a>
</div>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p><strong>Fiber</strong> for example, is one of weight loss&#8217;s little secrets. The main structural component of plants, fiber can&#8217;t be digested by the human body. Its primary purpose is to add bulk to the contents of your stomach and digestive tract, which helps move things along and keeps you regular. As a bonus, the extra bulk in your belly helps fill you up and keep you feeling full so you can limit your calorie intake. Having a fiber-rich shake as a snack or meal replacement each day just might be what you need to shed those extra pounds. Fiber-rich foods, such as fruits, vegetables and whole grains, tend to be healthy and low in energy density, or calories per gram. Eating a lot of low-energy-dense foods helps fill you up on fewer calories so you can control your calorie intake to lose weight. According to a review published in "Nutrition" in March 2005, dietary fiber intake is inversely associated with body weight; people who eat more fiber tend to weigh less and have less body fat.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Replacing one meal a day with a <a href="http://amzn.to/2AVVPPY">nutritious, high-fiber shake</a> can help you create the calorie deficit required for weight loss. To lose 1 to 2 pounds per week, which is considered a safe and healthy rate of weight loss, you need to trim 500 to 1,000 calories from your daily diet. If you normally go out for lunch with coworkers and take in 800 calories or more, skipping the lunch outing and whipping up a fiber-rich shake in the kitchen at your office can save you 500 calories. That one change is enough to lose 4 pounds in a month.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Programmers, software engineers, hackers, geeks, ready to buff up your overall energy and health? <a href="http://amzn.to/2AVVPPY">Try it</a> now:)</p>
</div>]]></description><link>https://live-smart.github.io/2017/11/30/Best-Diet-for-Programmers-Software-Engineers-Hackers-Geeks.html</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://live-smart.github.io/2017/11/30/Best-Diet-for-Programmers-Software-Engineers-Hackers-Geeks.html</guid><category><![CDATA[diet]]></category><category><![CDATA[programmers]]></category><category><![CDATA[software engineers]]></category><category><![CDATA[hackers]]></category><category><![CDATA[geeks]]></category><category><![CDATA[health]]></category><category><![CDATA[shake]]></category><category><![CDATA[fibre]]></category><category><![CDATA[fiber]]></category><category><![CDATA[yoghurt]]></category><category><![CDATA[weight loss]]></category><category><![CDATA[probiotics]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[Smart Buddy]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2017 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Sony WH-1000XM2 Noise Cancelling Wireless Headphone]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="sect2">
<h3 id="_what_are_the_sony_wh_1000xm2">What are the Sony WH-1000XM2?</h3>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>In 2016, the Trusted Reviews award for Best Headphones went to the Sony MDR-1000X, excellent wireless and noise-cancelling headphones with an intelligent set of features. The <a href="https://goo.gl/AjEyM7">Sony WH-1000XM2</a> are their successor, and they’re a little better in almost every way.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>The market is tougher now, and Sony faces fierce competition from the <a href="https://goo.gl/VVSSN1">Bose QuietComfort 35 II</a> and <a href="https://goo.gl/55w1xd">B&amp;W PX</a>. But the new <a href="https://goo.gl/AjEyM7">Sony WH-1000XM2</a> get so many things right it’s hard to fault them. They sound great, the noise cancellation is effective, and most of the features are genuinely useful.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>If you’re looking for an everyday pair of headphones, these are hard to beat.</p>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect2">
<h3 id="_design">Design</h3>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>The <a href="https://goo.gl/uua9y2">Sony MDR-1000X</a> had an excellent design that didn’t need fixing, so Sony has basically left it alone. That’s fine, since it meant the company could spare some resources towards expanding the <a href="https://goo.gl/AjEyM7">WH-1000XM2</a> range – check out the <a href="https://goo.gl/VPJvqq">Sony WF-1000X</a> wireless earbuds.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Anyway, the <a href="https://goo.gl/AjEyM7">Sony WH-1000XM2</a> are more of a facelift than a makeover – there are a few minor improvements over the original, but unless you’re really looking for them you probably won’t notice.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>They still look very smart, with the same streamlined silhouette and hardly any branding. The body is mainly plastic, with polished metal in the headband and good quality synthetic leather at the ears.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>The paintjob is a little different: the beige version is now closer to champagne gold, while the black version is more gunmetal greyish blue. This adds a little visual flair, but the overall effect is no less subtle. If you want something with an executive vibe, the <a href="https://goo.gl/ZxCqBW">Sony WH-1000XM2</a> will do nicely.</p>
</div>
<div class="imageblock">
<div class="content">
<a class="image" href="http://amzn.to/2japefG"><img src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/19504323/33707661-1abce4d4-db73-11e7-9563-da24f9f08f1c.png" alt="33707661 1abce4d4 db73 11e7 9563 da24f9f08f1c.png"></a>
</div>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>The synthetic leather on the outside of the ear cups has been swapped for a more tactile alternative. It’s less smooth to the touch – some might say it’s more plasticky – but I feel it’s thicker and tougher. I welcome this change, because the smooth finish of the original always seemed at risk of scratching. Now I feel a little less bad throwing them straight into my bag without first using the protective carry case.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>What hasn’t changed is the polyurethane foam stuffed into the headband and ear pads. They’re as squishy as ever, and the <a href="https://goo.gl/AjEyM7">Sony WH-1000XM2</a> are as comfortable as their predecessors. Clamp force is just right; they hold the sides of your head but never squeeze. As before, the headband expands with satisfying clicks. The earcups can fold inwards on hinges, as well as swivel flat.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>The buttons have been streamlined. Power/pairing remains where it is, but noise cancelling and ambient sound adjustment have been merged into one. That makes it a little harder to press the wrong thing, which might sound minor, but there’s value in being able to just get on with your listening.</p>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect2">
<h3 id="_features">Features</h3>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>The improvements to the features list is a lot less subtle. There have been quite a lot of tweaks and additions.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>The Bluetooth has been upgraded. The <a href="https://goo.gl/AjEyM7">Sony WH-1000XM2</a> are compatible with aptX HD, a higher quality Bluetooth format that can handle hi-res audio up to 24bit/48kHz. LDAC is also included, and it can handle 24bit/96kHz, but it’s a proprietary Sony format, limited to Sony devices. The left ear has an NFC chip for quicker Bluetooth pairing.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>The touch-sensitive control pad on the right ear cup has been tightened up, so your inputs feel more accurate and responsive.The Quick Attention mode, where you hold your palm to the right ear to mute, remains unchanged.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>The Ambient Sound feature is smarter. It still allows audio passthrough so you can be more aware of the outside world, but now it’s adaptive. The strength of noise cancellation will vary according to what you’re doing – sitting around, walking around, riding in vehicles or running for the bus.</p>
</div>
<div class="imageblock">
<div class="content">
<a class="image" href="http://amzn.to/2japefG"><img src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/19504323/33707728-5f5b2c22-db73-11e7-9974-1a5480a98fb0.png" alt="33707728 5f5b2c22 db73 11e7 9974 1a5480a98fb0.png"></a>
</div>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>The Optimizer feature has also been improved. It still scans the side of your head to measure how good the seal is, factoring in sunglasses or big hair and adjusting the sound accordingly, but now it uses a pressure sensor too.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Why? Sony says changes in atmospheric pressure can affect the way the drivers and noise-cancelling microphones work. The 1000XM2 measure the barometric pressure in your immediate surroundings, and then compensates the sound accordingly. The idea is that you should get the best noise cancellation the headphones can offer, no matter if you’re in a train or 35,000 feet in the air.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>In the time I had to test the Sony WH-1000XM2, I didn’t have any flights booked, so I can’t comment on the effectiveness of the pressure sensor. But the Optimizer feature definitely works, and I find myself re-calibrating the sound when I wear glasses.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>You can now tinker with the headphones with a mobile app. This lets you adjust the severity of the noise cancellation, or disable it entirely. You can also choose to prioritise connection stability over sound quality, or vice versa. That’s genuinely handy if you’re in a busy office or station and other people’s wireless signal interferes.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Less useful are the virtual positioning and virtual surround modes. The first lets you move the soundstage in front or around you; the second attempts to replicate the acoustics of spaces such as ‘concert hall’ or ‘arena’. I wouldn’t bother with these as they just make the music sound worse. If you want really want to mess with your sound quality, I’d just play with the EQ settings.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>There’s also the DSEE (Digital Sound Enhancement Engine) processing, which claims to upscale compressed audio. This was on all the time in the previous version, but now you have the option to turn it off. I’d leave it on as it actually helps a little.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>It would be reasonable to assume all these features sap battery life, but there is actually more juice than ever. The original 1000X lasted up to 20 hours, but the <a href="https://goo.gl/AjEyM7">Sony WH-1000XM2</a> goes up to 30 hours (wireless) or 40 hours (wired).</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>There’s even a quick charge feature – 10 minutes at the mains will give you 70 minutes’ play time. A few headphone manufacturers have switched over to USB-C for power, but Sony has stuck with the ubiquitous microUSB.</p>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect2">
<h3 id="_performance">Performance</h3>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>When it comes to noise cancellation, the <a href="https://goo.gl/AjEyM7">Sony WH-1000XM2</a> are some of the best you can buy. I put them through a varied assault course including excited cafe chatter, rattling train carriages, roadworks with pneumatic drills and speakers blasting plane engine noises – the <a href="https://goo.gl/AjEyM7">WH-1000XM2</a> dialled all that down to a whisper.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>They’re not quite as deadly silent as the <a href="https://goo.gl/VVSSN1">Bose QuietComfort 35 II</a>, but it’s not a huge difference, and they’re more effective than the <a href="https://goo.gl/55w1xd">B&amp;W PX</a>. I could (and did) fall asleep listening to these headphones on a train.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>It’s not just the effective noise cancellation that impresses me – it’s the smart element that Sony has introduced. The headphone app works with the accelerometers in your phone to determine whether you’re at rest, in motion or in transit – and the levels of noise cancellation really do change accordingly.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>In ‘Staying’ mode, the headphones let some voices in so I could still tell if a colleagues wanted my attention. In ‘Walking’ mode, they let in more ambient noise so I could be aware of approaching traffic. As soon as I got onto a train, Transport mode kicked in and noise cancellation was dialled up to maximum. You can turn this off, but I love it.</p>
</div>
<div class="imageblock">
<div class="content">
<a class="image" href="http://amzn.to/2japefG"><img src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/19504323/33708007-36ebc052-db74-11e7-866e-3dcaebd9a4f4.png" alt="33708007 36ebc052 db74 11e7 866e 3dcaebd9a4f4.png"></a>
</div>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>As for audio performance, the <a href="https://goo.gl/AjEyM7">WH-1000XM2</a> have many of the traits I admired so much about the original. They’re a hugely entertaining listen, thanks to a combination of hard-hitting dynamism, boundless energy and impressive rhythmic precision.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>That agility partly comes down to its impressive articulation and neutral tonal balance. No part of the frequency range feels exaggerated, and everything is nicely defined. There’s no flab to the bass, the midrange is direct and succinct, and the treble is clean, free of sibilance. It’s a very tidy presentation.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Compared to the original MDR-1000X, I found the <a href="https://goo.gl/AjEyM7">WH-1000XM2</a> to be a little clearer and more hard-hitting. But the audio components are the same, so I’m going to put this down to the fact that I was using aptX HD compatible music devices (an LG G6 and Astell &amp; Kern AK70). In wired mode, there was no discernable difference.</p>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect2">
<h3 id="_why_buy_the_a_href_https_goo_gl_zxcqbw_sony_wh_1000xm2_a">Why buy the <a href="https://goo.gl/ZxCqBW">Sony WH-1000XM2</a>?</h3>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>The <a href="https://goo.gl/AjEyM7">Sony WH-1000XM2</a> have improved on their predecessors in nearly every way. The physical design has been tweaked for the better, the audio performance is stronger, and the noise cancellation is smarter.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>So the competition is tougher this year, but that’s not a problem for Sony. The <a href="https://goo.gl/VVSSN1">Bose QuietComfort 35 II</a> offer more effective noise cancellation, but they’re not as musically talented. The <a href="https://goo.gl/55w1xd">B&amp;W PX</a> are the best-sounding of the lot, but they’re not as smart or as good at noise-cancelling.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Sony, meanwhile, have excellent all-rounders that excel in every department.</p>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect2">
<h3 id="_verdict">Verdict</h3>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>The best just got better.</p>
</div>
</div>]]></description><link>https://live-smart.github.io/2017/11/19/Sony-WH-1000X-M-Noise-Cancelling-Wireless-Headphone.html</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://live-smart.github.io/2017/11/19/Sony-WH-1000X-M-Noise-Cancelling-Wireless-Headphone.html</guid><category><![CDATA[noise-cancelling]]></category><category><![CDATA[earphone]]></category><category><![CDATA[sony]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[Smart Buddy]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2017 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Allergy, Dust Mites, and Solution]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="paragraph">
<p>Have you ever experienced symptoms of allergy such as rhinitis, nasal congestion, asthma, urticaria? I&#8217;ve had serious rhinitis and nasal congestion during sleep since I was born, and absolutely no idea what has gone wrong. I tried different treatments such as ephedrine nasal spray, septum reconstructomy, polypectomy, none of which really worked. I&#8217;ve been waking up during mid of night just to get some air before I suffocate. That is until recently after I found a solution for this, one that solves it for good.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>During my research, I found that my symptoms might be related to allergy to something, but I had no idea what that was. Some further digging pointed me to dust mites.</p>
</div>
<div class="quoteblock">
<blockquote>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>The house dust mite (HDM) is a major perennial allergen source and a significant cause of allergic rhinitis and allergic asthma.</p>
</div>
</blockquote>
<div class="attribution">
&#8212; Respiratory allergy caused by house dust mites: What do we really know?
</div>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p><a href="http://www.jacionline.org/article/S0091-6749(14)01482-1/abstract?cc=y=">Link to it</a></p>
</div>
<div class="quoteblock">
<blockquote>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Dust mites may be the most common trigger of year-round allergies and asthma.</p>
</div>
</blockquote>
<div class="attribution">
&#8212; Dust Mite Allergy
</div>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p><a href="http://www.aafa.org/page/dust-mite-allergy.aspx">Link to it</a></p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Since I don&#8217;t have sofa and carpets, a major point where dust mites can thrive should be inferrably my bed or more specifically the mattress. How can I get those tiny bugs out of my mattress? I did quite a few research on this. There are youtube videos introducing heating methods for killing dust mites, which are more or less one off and won&#8217;t solve the problem over time. What I need is something repeatable and that can solve the perennial problem the sustainable way.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>That leads me to vacuum based solutions. I found <a href="https://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B01910SH8G/ref=as_li_qf_sp_asin_il_tl?ie=UTF8&amp;tag=livesmart08-20&amp;camp=1789&amp;creative=9325&amp;linkCode=as2&amp;creativeASIN=B01910SH8G&amp;linkId=2352c1144a335df35af1b62d36ea86d3">Rainbow</a></p>
</div>
<div class="imageblock">
<div class="content">
<a class="image" href="https://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B01910SH8G/ref=as_li_tl?ie=UTF8&camp=1789&creative=9325&creativeASIN=B01910SH8G&linkCode=as2&tag=livesmart08-20&linkId=de60bbbcc8e3cabf92f504791468f3a0"><img src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/19504323/33869807-d2dfbb1a-df45-11e7-9c59-b7122a26bfec.png" alt="33869807 d2dfbb1a df45 11e7 9c59 b7122a26bfec.png"></a>
</div>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>But this looks more like overkill and really requires some good space to store it. A better option is <a href="https://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B00SMLJPKA/ref=as_li_qf_sp_asin_il_tl?ie=UTF8&amp;tag=livesmart08-20&amp;camp=1789&amp;creative=9325&amp;linkCode=as2&amp;creativeASIN=B00SMLJPKA&amp;linkId=e022a1567aed7d0cfa75b89fcb880ae7">Dyson V6</a>. It&#8217;s completely cordless and battery-based. A full charge as I tested can last around 20 minutes of working at its full capacity (strong mode). The suction power is really outstanding. With the <a href="https://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B0017R6ZO0/ref=as_li_qf_sp_asin_il_tl?ie=UTF8&amp;tag=livesmart08-20&amp;camp=1789&amp;creative=9325&amp;linkCode=as2&amp;creativeASIN=B0017R6ZO0&amp;linkId=955f051110948cca65849f26d9c09ea3">mini turbine head</a> (see below) which comes with V6 Absolute model, I&#8217;m basically able to suck all dust mites, their remains, my own dead skin and dandruff out of my mattress.</p>
</div>
<div class="imageblock">
<div class="content">
<a class="image" href="https://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B00062MT7E/ref=as_li_tl?ie=UTF8&camp=1789&creative=9325&creativeASIN=B00062MT7E&linkCode=as2&tag=livesmart08-20&linkId=9aac2ee60d48806f4ba60b358837bc8b"><img src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/19504323/33869902-495d8664-df46-11e7-9582-3460be6fbc32.png" alt="33869902 495d8664 df46 11e7 9582 3460be6fbc32.png"></a>
</div>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>It surprises me that a clean normal looking mattress can contain such amount of powder like stuff:</p>
</div>
<div class="imageblock">
<div class="content">
<a class="image" href="https://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B00SMLJPKA/ref=as_li_qf_sp_asin_il_tl?ie=UTF8&tag=livesmart08-20&camp=1789&creative=9325&linkCode=as2&creativeASIN=B00SMLJPKA&linkId=e022a1567aed7d0cfa75b89fcb880ae7"><img src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/19504323/16232379/dc0349ce-37fc-11e6-9514-2fd02a2a3f0e.jpg" alt="dc0349ce 37fc 11e6 9514 2fd02a2a3f0e.jpg"></a>
</div>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>And much better sleep for me ever after the first campaign of removing dust mites!</p>
</div>]]></description><link>https://live-smart.github.io/2016/06/17/Allergy-Dust-Mites-and-Solution.html</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://live-smart.github.io/2016/06/17/Allergy-Dust-Mites-and-Solution.html</guid><category><![CDATA[allergy]]></category><category><![CDATA[dust mite]]></category><category><![CDATA[bed]]></category><category><![CDATA[mattress]]></category><category><![CDATA[vacuum]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[Smart Buddy]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2016 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Shoes and Knee Pain]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div id="preamble">
<div class="sectionbody">
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Knee pain is commonly witnessed among people of all ages. Causes can vary but the most significant yet often overlooked one is shoes. How would you pick a pair of shoes that would ease or prevent knee damage / knee pain?</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>There are 3 major factors that contribute to the comfort level of shoes.</p>
</div>
<div class="olist arabic">
<ol class="arabic">
<li>
<p>Arch support</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Ankle support</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Heel Cushioning</p>
</li>
</ol>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>&#8203;<br></p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect3">
<h4 id="_arch_support">Arch Support</h4>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>The arch is perhaps the most important structural feature of our feet, which bear 200,000 to 300,000 lbs. of weight each mile we walk. Arches absorb the brunt of the pressure our bodies thrust upon our feet with each stride. Properly supporting the arch can prevent a variety of musculoskeletal problems that can lead to inactivity and even disability.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p><span class="image"><img src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/19504323/15632485/b4cd98a8-25c5-11e6-8c46-2b222e525c75.jpg" alt="b4cd98a8 25c5 11e6 8c46 2b222e525c75.jpg"></span></p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>&#8203;<br></p>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect3">
<h4 id="_ankle_support">Ankle Support</h4>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>It really depends on what kind of ankle you have. If yours is iffy, it would generally be safer to pick a pair of shoes that provides great ankle support.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Here&#8217;s a lacing technique that would help as well:</p>
</div>
<iframe width="640" height="360" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/Cq-Ar0zzFTI?rel=0" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>&#8203;<br></p>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect3">
<h4 id="_heel_cushioning">Heel Cushioning</h4>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>The risk of knee injury is increased by physical changes as joint cartilage that absorbs shock, becomes thinner with aging, weight gain and muscle loss. Great running shoes are designed to cushion your feet, which in turn takes stress off your knees.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p><span class="image"><img src="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/19504323/15452729/4993684a-202c-11e6-9efb-232c71ebd5c8.jpg" alt="4993684a 202c 11e6 9efb 232c71ebd5c8.jpg"></span></p>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect3">
<h4 id="_recommendations">Recommendations</h4>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>When it comes to running safe and in comfort, maximalist shoes are definitely the number one option to go for. And guess who&#8217;s the king of maximalists?</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Introducing Hoka One One. It is a French manufacturing company that designs and markets generously soled and extremely light weight running shoes for distance runners. Noted for their light weight and maximal cushioning, Hoka running shoes are dubbed as "maximalist shoes", in contrast to minimalist shoes. In 2010, it introduced the original <a href="http://amzn.to/1TTW0zT">Mafate</a>, a running shoe boasting two to three times the amount of cushioning as other running shoes on the market.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>So which model would you fit into? Here I picked a list of Hokas that are best for knee protection:</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p><strong>Vanquish 2</strong></p>
</div>
<div class="imageblock">
	<div class="content">

<a class="image" href="http://www.amazon.com/Hoka-One-Vanquish-Black-Running/dp/B00ZUYP0CY/ref=as_li_ss_il?ie=UTF8&qid=1465035208&sr=8-1&keywords=hoka+one+one+vanquish+2&linkCode=li2&tag=livesmart08-20&linkId=364785b81d6e9356b85cab7a91eae30d" target="_blank"><img border="0" src="//ws-na.amazon-adsystem.com/widgets/q?_encoding=UTF8&ASIN=B00ZUYP0CY&Format=_SL500_&ID=AsinImage&MarketPlace=US&ServiceVersion=20070822&WS=1&tag=livesmart08-20" ></a><img src="//ir-na.amazon-adsystem.com/e/ir?t=livesmart08-20&l=li2&o=1&a=B00ZUYP0CY" width="1" height="1" border="0" alt="" style="border:none !important; margin:0px !important;" />

    </div>
	<div class="title">

Hoka completely overhauled this cushy neutral shoe for 2016, making it lighter and more energetic. Weights: 9.8 oz. (men’s 9.0); 8.3 oz. (women’s 7.0). Heel-Toe Offset: 5mm; 32mm (heel), 27mm (forefoot)

    </div>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>&#8203;<br></p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p><strong>Bondi 4</strong></p>
</div>
<div class="imageblock">
	<div class="content">

<a href="http://www.amazon.com/Hoka-One-Bondi-Directoire-Running/dp/B01071HR84/ref=as_li_ss_il?ie=UTF8&qid=1465039586&sr=8-1&keywords=hoka+one+one+bondi+4&linkCode=li3&tag=livesmart08-20&linkId=9d6d5b6a3abdd83073e5acb0716c1567" target="_blank"><img border="0" src="//ws-na.amazon-adsystem.com/widgets/q?_encoding=UTF8&ASIN=B01071HR84&Format=_SL500_&ID=AsinImage&MarketPlace=US&ServiceVersion=20070822&WS=1&tag=livesmart08-20" ></a><img src="//ir-na.amazon-adsystem.com/e/ir?t=livesmart08-20&l=li3&o=1&a=B01071HR84" width="1" height="1" border="0" alt="" style="border:none !important; margin:0px !important;" />

    </div>
	<div class="title">

With one of the thickest midsoles in the marketplace, the Bondi is in an extreme class of high-off-the-ground, oversized cushioning shoes. But it’s not just the amount of cushioning, it’s the balance of the shoe and its unique design features—specifically the rockered profile, beveled heel and significant toe spring—that make running in the Bondi 4 such an exalted experience. weights: 10.6 oz. (men’s), 9.4 oz. (women’s); heel-toe offset: 4mm; 37mm (heel), 33mm (forefoot) for men; 34mm (heel), 30mm (forefoot) for women

    </div>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>&#8203;<br></p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p><strong>Clifton 2</strong></p>
</div>
<div class="imageblock">
	<div class="content">

<a href="http://www.amazon.com/Hoka-One-Clifton-Directoire-Running/dp/B011PM8K12/ref=as_li_ss_il?ie=UTF8&qid=1465039691&sr=8-1&keywords=hoka+one+one+clifton+3&linkCode=li2&tag=livesmart08-20&linkId=2bd56d3fe715fa108766ec3f0553388f" target="_blank"><img border="0" src="//ws-na.amazon-adsystem.com/widgets/q?_encoding=UTF8&ASIN=B011PM8K12&Format=_SL500_&ID=AsinImage&MarketPlace=US&ServiceVersion=20070822&WS=1&tag=livesmart08-20" ></a><img src="//ir-na.amazon-adsystem.com/e/ir?t=livesmart08-20&l=li2&o=1&a=B011PM8K12" width="1" height="1" border="0" alt="" style="border:none !important; margin:0px !important;" />

    </div>
	<div class="title">

Hoka made a few small but significant tweaks to the award-winning Clifton for 2016, most notably making it a few millimeters wider in the forefoot and replacing the overlays on the upper with a sleeker, seamless TPU-reinforced mesh. ($130, 5mm heel-toe offset, 8.6 oz.)

    </div>
</div>
</div>]]></description><link>https://live-smart.github.io/2016/03/05/Shoes-and-Knee-Pain.html</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://live-smart.github.io/2016/03/05/Shoes-and-Knee-Pain.html</guid><category><![CDATA[knee]]></category><category><![CDATA[knee pain]]></category><category><![CDATA[knee protection]]></category><category><![CDATA[shoe]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[Smart Buddy]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sat, 05 Mar 2016 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>